In the shadows of the forest where the outcasts sing
She walks like a flame in a serpentine ring
Emerald eyes in the hush of the night
Truth in her breath, revelation in her bite
The drums of the eggstiles drum under her feet
Down bends words twist time
Yeah, the star don't die
Victory born with a BJ in my eyes
Step in the dark, I turn shadow to light
Cold on the rise, we don't run from the night
Fire in my chest, let the mantra it deep
Wake up the dead, make the sleepers all speak
Name in your blood and the truth won't climb
Say psychics, hell it
than the pitch black dark
Venus in my ore, yeah, they charmed too real
Mercury in mine, everything I touch heals
Jupiter crowns it, and I on my fate
Saturn on my heels, I was built to be great
Like excel at a rewrite time
I don't lead sheep, I awaken the wolves
I don't want praise, I dismantle old rules
Mirror break, mind stay true in the cracks
Follow my step, get your whole soul back
I speak for the loss, for the brave
For the strange, for the ones reshaping their life on the flame
Shadow don't scare me, I romance the void
Turn chaos to scripture, your fear I destroy
Got a shady old name
Panther on a path and her icy eyes
You can't hide sin from a creature that wise
Follow us, rise like a storm reborn
Every chance we drop another veil gets torn
Yet it's the cold, but the fire's all yours
I'm just a spark at the edge of the door
Psyche in the flesh, yet a star don't
My shadow's already halfway gone My heart beats walkin' out without me
Bless me, break me Either way I'm yours
You keep callin' it salvation I keep callin' it a lie
I'm stretched thin in the void Peranoia low round my mind
If I ever swore I'd rise up That promise died under my tongue
These demons don't harm my thoughts now They live in my blood
Watching serpents on the ceiling drip
If you don't like my apocalypse
Say what your chest don't whisper it
I'm trying to be better, but the better I try
The worse I'll break
I will buy, I will slow fate
That the instruments I never agreed to pay
Didn't learn the lesson
Didn't learn from all the
Didn't learn from love, so get me enough
Never been a man I claimed I'd be
Had all the things, had all the lines
Now the mirror won't look back at me
She'd fix my fractures and carve the name into my spine
Bring me till the light goes out
I'm blind to every holy sign
You're the last one who'll be around me
Gravity and human form
Touch me till I feel something
Bring me till I'm finally born
And I'm drifting, drifting
With the blood on the bed she's glistening
Heaven wants to watch me listening to the last echo in my chest
If love is a curse then I'm obsessed
I'm a place of dying slow
With the sunlight on my bed
You say you want me to stay
So you're, yeah, you're still here, that's why you're, that's why you're my number one. Okay,
one second, one second, one second guys be right with you.
Yeah, let's see.
Yeah, I don't know how long this would be today, but
I'm going to do a nice little up live.
Oh, you got you get snow love. Well, maybe
be a little bit longer. I mean, talk about Jamie's been here first, but, you know,
for months, but for a year. Okay.
Okay, got it. Okay. Come up.
Hi. There we go.
It's first in my heart. Have you ever heard ladies first?
Have you ever heard that term ladies first?
Hello.
So, no offense to Jamie. The second is that he's be writing history. Well
That's true, that's that is that part is true, but Jamie knows that
You know, and it's like a little bit, you know
I'm a little bit slow sometimes, you know
your first your first Samantha second, I don't know. Samantha's usually first too
but
And I know, oh yeah, so I did un-mod like almost frankly everybody, but
some people get their mods back, right? Like today, but I think in the future it'll be like,
you know, actual, you know, cult members will get, we'll probably have the mods, like, you know,
she is okay. Well, when she, when I see her again, she had it, I might, I might take care of that, but
You know, I am uh, I do have to change a few things like for example
You know, I do like I didn't have some fun in the open panels, but it's like
At first maybe it was like 50 50% fun like 50 50 like right now, it's like 90% not fun
It's also
You know getting like ridiculous, so I think from now on
You don't want a modest little respect. Well, I don't know who you are. Who are you? I know you're my discord. Are you?
So who are you? What's your name? Where like what I just I don't get it
I can't just show up here if anyone can have it like a screen name, right?
It's your picture. It's just like a like a dark dark figure
Who is that?
Someone in the shadows. Who could that be?
It's a matter who's first it's not a it's not a race. I show is on a race
Experience
Yeah, mr. Yumi is actually almost everybody's oh, yeah, you're the first thumbs up. Thank you. Well
Keep keep coming and keep doing thumbs up, you know, but
Unfortunately, there's a lot of people that are incognito and
Things like that. And so one of the first things I'm gonna make sure of is like I
Will be true I'm gonna not let myself be disrespected on my show. Oh, but see look at this so much respect boy
Are you Chris K and lesser Chris K? You're about to get banned. You don't tell me to show you respect
Because respect is earned right you like the background. Thank you. Is there anyone?
Thank you
I did it. Yeah, I do have a few new new graphics and things and
Pay a lot of work into this I'm working on the website still you can go you can go and see the progress a cult of psyche
but I think yeah, the memberships are up, but and
It's like there is a free initiate the initiatory level is free
You know what and initially the initiates can always be in chat and they can always
Watch watch this show on
You know and there's some introductory materials, too, so it's not that's that's good, but
There's like the figures levels this I'm gonna run it like I need to run it more like
The new cult it is so but anyway, there's been revelations recently
right
It's like a nut and I feel kind of dumb
Feel kind of like a dumb dumb. I feel like a dumb dumb
I have allowed a lot of people here with no good intentions for me.
It's okay. Yeah, it's okay, Jamie. You're fine.
I know you, but yeah, there's been people with some pretty bad intentions towards me,
and it's like, don't feel that way.
Well, Jamie, it's true, and I mean, I wish I could have shown you some of the things I saw today.
For example, I don't know. Ever since the beginning of the show, I didn't meet somebody that I thought was a great friend and a really cool and neat person and we both love cats and all that stuff.
Oh yeah, I'm not a dumb dumb. I was being sarcastic a little bit. So girls would call me a dumb dumb, right?
And I was I was being a dumb dumb. I was being a dumb dumb because I was like trying to make everyone happy
But you know, they said there's some people there's sometimes
People that no matter what you do
No matter what I would do
They're not gonna be happy. They're only happy when I'm unhappy. That's that's that's some people, right?
How how would
How can you survive like that? How can you survive? Right? Some people that I think didn't think by show would still be here, right?
Oh, I mean I
Did some dumb things. I believed I
Believed that some people that I thought
Were or friends or not friends. Hey, Paul. Oh
Yeah, so and I don't know yes, I'm
How are you doing Apollo?
Yeah, I figured some things out right. I figured some things up but um
Because I'm seeing somebody else and I can't go into too much detail about it because you know
I have a tendency to blab about everything and like give away way too much of the game and explain over explain and stuff
But I'll say I
See what happened to me happening to other people or other yeah others, right?
And it's like, wow.
It's like, why didn't I see that before?
I see people that I trusted as mods,
not having good intentions for me.
Not like, you know,
actually more like, you know, spies
or kind of actually more like sleeper agents or.
Also people have a people who just send to like watch me on the panel and then report or
Do some bit do the bidding of an evil queen
But yeah, that's all in the past you know and I do have to say
Thank you to a few people because like only a few people would
Verteling me. I mean, there are probably more than a few. I wish I would have listened to some more of them, right?
But yeah, so I just want to tell you a few few few things planned I am probably gonna be having shorter
lives they're probably gonna be
Some some lectures some of you know some things like that not lectures like I'm boring but interesting information
I want to share everyone doesn't make mistakes. You're watching please chase is checking if you're okay. You thought I might have been me. I
Don't have the car, but they're the chasing somebody walking on up in the street
and
Like why would you think it would be me?
Please chase
strange
Loose schoom schoom Mason. Oh, I want schoom a so one eight seven. Do I know you the stolen car?
You know, why do you think I would steal a car?
I'm a kind of person that steals cars
Look how these new people how to cope with how great there's just these brand new people have nowhere coming here
Same very strange things, right?
Okay, also I will be having I think I think someone may I talked to somebody they made an analogy that I have like a
I had a saloon door, right? I never know
Well, right, but it's like
It didn't be kind of a long shot like
But chaotic order of nature, right? You don't ever think someone would do anything
Desperation scared
What does that mean
He's desperate. He's scared
You know, I like actually came I'm actually not this monster
That I've been painted out to be right you probably still a car I was able to oh, it's come you were able to a lot
Yeah, he's gone. You're able to you know who it is
Scum. Okay. I scum. I scum. I know who you are. Yeah, um
Yeah, so anyway
Just meeting this person yeah, it was yeah led to some exciting things, you know, I thought this person was really cool and
You know, they
Have been along a little bit longer than me or even a lot longer and knew the ropes and you had a knew how to
work this thing, you know, you
It did pay off in a lot of ways. I did have a really, you know, a great rise, but I had
a pretty bad fall, right? Maybe that was all part of the plan. The problem is, you don't
Scared or desperation scared. What'd you say it? Yeah, it's okay. Yeah. Yeah. Hey Chanel
Okay, I just but yeah, I think yeah, I will be giving like some people
Right like for some people I do right away. I want it
Give honorary, you know, memberships to or do you consider part of the cult like there?
Okay, I think that's a good person
But yeah, I hope nobody's like nobody nobody should get offended over mods or anything
I mean, it's like mods really an honorary position and I do it
It's like the people with wrenches. You can just know that they are the cult members, right?
Yeah, she got it. She got it Chanel got it
But Jamie it's I mean I need to like there's some because I did I do have some kind of inside information about some things
Okay, so I need to
Be more careful about who I'm mod because there's some mods that maybe just want to like
Run over to somebody else and tell them all this information or
Start drama, but if my mods are doing things people don't like they blame the streamer. Well, it's okay
You know what because I'm not doing this for
Then I'm doing this for like hey flirty diamonds. I'm doing this for people like here. I'm not a flirty diamond
You're an honorary member of flirty. Okay. I mean I'm not on where you are member. You're cold. You're the cult, okay?
It's a cult of psyche
Yeah, but you know there's
You know some people
We're telling me you know exactly what was happening and I wasn't listening, you know
I feel like pretty dumb about that, but yeah, I feel like
It's kind of set up to eventually try to fail this in the air moji is what do what you want. Thank you
Yeah, I'm I'm not trying to it's like that's why I mean if I was trying to please people
I would just be doing what I was doing the open panels
Um, it is it's the cult of psyche k u l t of psyche not satan. No
Well, where'd you get satan from who said satan?
Actually, we do have some patron deities of the cult that's kind of, you know, for the members to know about and everybody else to wonder about.
Got some really, really cool stuff going on.
And I feel like I meant to do this, but yeah, I wasn't supposed to be here. So I think, I think the plan was when my, like, you know, by the time my channel got taken down, I would be
I'd be ready to quit or just you know, so hated nobody would overcome. I know you I know you're you're good. Yeah
So I
You know, but that's like business and I know but I'm seeing like people that I really cared about like start to like just treat me
You're like really bad
I was like, what's that about?
Like, do they ever like me, right?
There's like a buddy trolling.
I need to rewrite that chapter of my trollopedia
because maybe it's something I didn't really understand
as much as I should have.
It's kind of like when people like pretend to be your friend.
You know, I have no idea people are their ad site.
I have no idea people.
Haitian, yeah, diamond, yeah.
I do have great people here.
And there's people like, you know.
It is stuck by me despite it, but those people that were it was just they were just designed to not
Stay by here and just designed to
Make me look bad
You know
Not succeed or right, but you know what at the end of the day
It's my fault. It's my fault because I should have figured it out earlier
I should have listened to some people that were telling me the truth
problem is like
Wasn't too many people that were
But and I was drinking a lot and I was I was being a wet brain, right and I was
Letting people take over my show is letting people disrespect I was like, oh, this is how it's supposed to be this pan
You know, it's like some of the things going on in that panel versus community are so disgusting or really disgusting.
Like I would say.
not borderline, evil, I would say evil.
And I used to say, oh, I love everybody.
I wanna love everybody.
Everyone has good in them.
And yeah, people take good in them and stuff like that,
but I think that the evil has taken over.
Hey, Mason, how are you?
I think the evil has taken over for some people.
And it's not funny to play with people, people's minds, right?
To like
You know, and I thought I'd been to enough gaslighting and like narcissistic abuse to understand that
Build the shadow
I'm looking good. Thank you so much
Thank you
So anyway, it's the herd mentality if you started the psyche hate it was just joining me part of something entertainment
Well, yeah, and I do hope to entertain but I'm gonna do I mean now what now I'm gonna do what I came to do
Not only entertain but like help teach
Bring light
Accepts people you know I now that I've been cast away and discarded
thrown in the trash by so many people for like no no good reason right just
Just to do it or just to make somebody else happy or I
Seem like a soft and kind soul. Yeah, people take advantage of kind people, right? So I decided
It's okay to hate, but I hate hate, you know, I hate evil and it's like and then you know
I think I talked to somebody today made a good point
They're like, hey, you know love the sin love the sinner hate the sin
Like and some people do have this like dark shadow. That's kind of taken over
They're good, right?
Yeah
And I know and I oh my god, and I was so disrespected by some people that and I was I made mistakes
I made a lot of mistakes, right?
But I
Forgive myself for that you digress. Yeah, I forgive myself for the mistakes
I wish I didn't take so long for me to figure shit out, but you know once I did
Quick quick like lightning bolt. It's like a light lightning flash revelations. Oh, what happened?
Hold on. I'm sorry. Hold on. I just figure some shit out
There you go
So we're not I'm not gonna just gonna have the so someone said I have like a show my show was like a saloon
It was like you just think this is a saloon door and the saloon door opens
And then other people just sit up here for hours and hours on the panel some people
90% of the people like I could have done without even talking to you, right?
No one here is a friend. I know there's a few there's a few I
Do consider a few but just a few probably on one hand
The true like really true
Maybe a little bit maybe for me. I'm lucky enough. Maybe someday. There'll be two hands, right?
My big dick psychic. Wow. I like that. I have some BDE. That's nice
Yeah, won't be saved will you be saved will you be saved I
Don't know what we say people say people say friendly and I gotta say this we're both from LA
It's about respect the internet doesn't show respect
well you get the respect that you accept right or you're treated you're
kind of like getting the or the disrespect I just disrespected right you
know a lot of people here don't like tarot to the point of like you know just
just trying almost like destroying anything in my tarot tarot business right
Cuz I
Should have seen it and I shouldn't have put up with it. I
Do love tarot and I'm also it's like the ironic part is I am really good at it, but it's like
You know
So, yeah, Jamie and a lecture are loyal. Yeah, don't hesitate. But yeah, but the rest because oh, yeah
But it but especially especially one person that was a big big part of everything, right?
What was their intention?
To get to get me a little
You know a little a little fired up a little bigger and then
Like that I just
Like a back draft right suck all the air out of it cleared out. Oh, yeah, well, thank you and I've got I have so many
What is the what is be to allow that?
I don't know. Why does she allow HIV Awakens Tarot in the chat?
Why does she
Get mad at people to do the same that she does the exact same things, right?
Why why did she get to run my show? I don't know. I don't know why I let her like say
Oh mod this person. I had this person named Gish modded and then I had an uncomfortable feeling with that
Unmodded this person Gish
Oh, you know, she was like, hmm, you're on the right track, Doofy, but, but, but, uh, don't
I'm not, don't I'm not, don't I'm not, I was not, don't do, and I was like, oh my gosh,
and I was trying to, it's okay, I don't care.
She can watch, she can watch me rise, watch, you know, um, but again, I'm not going to
be mentioning, I'm not going to be really talking about her, um, in the future.
She discarded me pretty ruthlessly and but the whole thing was I
The first place I just fell in love with something that wasn't real, right?
But I forgive I forgive and I wish I wish her the best in her endeavors and I
Did learn a lot out of it. Wow. Now. I'm like a grown. I'm in a better place to
Help other people maybe
I've been wounded a little bit
I'm still coming out of the fog you know what fog means it's fear obligation and guilt
Okay
It was thanks
And so I've been in a fog and then alcohol all the alcohol and you know, all this stuff doesn't make it better, right?
And just like
Wanting to like please, you know, people please are right. That's one of the worst things
because
How about like please myself? It's gonna please yourself, too
Oh, you know, they always what maybe you want to like make your you know people that you really love happy how about like
I was trying to make people that I could never make happy happy that would never be happy that would only be happy if I was unhappy
So that's like that's I'm not gonna
Heart like you know hurt myself for you know, I want I want all of us to be happy
But so it's like but so I'll say if you're not interested in
If you're only here for like open panels and drama and meet and then people say the N word and, and, and people doc saying and, you know, follow each other and then demanding or demanding to come on panels and stuff like that.
I mean, and then just like expecting like, what do you think I want to be here.
But I won't be here much longer if I if I was going in that in the direction I was going my chance either the channel be taken down
Which is constantly under attack
And
It's not so it's not safe just to have an open panel, right?
So I need to have people I actually want to talk to and so
You know I
Will say probably the members will get a you know
Maybe it's possible people can sponsor panels. Maybe maybe I'll do some of that
but I'll you know also
I'll have to make some decisions that I don't know exactly what's not like where I'm going to go what I'm going to do
But I'll make the decision and I'm not going to be told what to do or like, you know, count into anything or the
you know
I'm not a not just someone to laugh at like which is basically what I've been treated like we're cool Mason. We're cool
We're very cool
I'm not gonna like
Just like let people up on the panel for hours just to sit there
So if I let somebody up, I want to talk to them, right?
I'm taking the power back.
I have to.
Maybe I've made illusions to try it,
to try to do that before.
And it's like, I needed to, I needed a lightning bolt.
Have I been playing any video games, man?
This is a video game I'm playing.
Streaming, YouTube streaming is the biggest video game, right?
I'm playing the biggest, the most serious video game
in the world.
YouTube streaming is called.
Yeah
a little bit like chess in a few ways and
fortunately
My opponent my biggest opponent made a miscalculation when they they moved me next to a queen
It did they thought would
you know
Have a conflict with or something like that or destroy me or something actually
That queen I love, you know, and I and so then one thing leads to another slowly
These people that
We're not supposed to be talking or discussing or figuring things out to figure things out, but
It really wasn't until today that I got really really really strong information
How'd I figure it out
Seeing myself and somebody else. So I figured it out
Seeing seeing seeing it happening to somebody else
Exactly down to like a script
I'm not gonna give too much information about it. It's like gonna be
It's kind of like if you know, you know
You know, you know, if you don't know
Ask somebody else
I'm not gonna be a name of names and you know, just giving away all the
Knowledge I have just
So I can like be criticized about it and told I'm wrong and argue and argued about it
I'll just say I know it's like a gnosis. It's like a knowing
It's well now it's painfully obvious right to me, but I
Needed that
So you said you never really should have you can tell something that's going on
Yeah, well, who I mean, let me know like if you're new in the check because I've seen a lot of new people
Just let me know like who you are like a word. What your name is usually I know. I know it's like the ad
But yeah
Ever since the like I mean, I might have a discord all I'm saying is that
I'm just gonna be in charge now.
I'm gonna be in charge.
Yeah, respect me, respect the child.
Just like when I was disrespected by people I loved,
I was like, did they ever love me
or were they just pretending, right?
They were pretending.
Some of it was obvious, some are still pretending.
Lot just got sick of it and just like, just did the discard.
But now that I've been discarded and I know how it feels to be just like discarded by so many people
Some people leave and then and then some turn on turn on me for really no reason. I
mean, I maybe I
Didn't
Maybe I did make mistakes. I don't know. I know I certainly did but my biggest mistake was just
putting my love and
the wrong people
It's like, how do you say the killer's inside the house, right?
It's like, you have some of the best, some of your best friends,
you think of your best friend is actually the killer, right?
It's like a movie, movie trope, there's like a movie called,
is there's a babysitter, it's babysitting and all of a sudden,
like there's, you know, there's some killer and.
Then she starts hearing like she starts getting these phone calls or something like that and then
These weird phone calls and she keeps you know calls the phone company and then also throughout the night
They're like we're finding the person we're finding that the we're tracing the call
We're tracing the call but by and all of a sudden you get a call from the operator
They're calling from inside the house
Right it too brute right now Brutus. It's like it's you what you Brutus you you my friend my friend Brutus
You you were the one conspiring
to like destroy me my most trusted advisor in general
What it was a jealousy just that or game a game you play like what was the point of it?
just to
Laugh at me there was a
Just make me like some kind of like laughing stock like literally stock like a cow
And it's like and then oh
But that your plan didn't go quite as you thought it would because slowly
some people they thought you brought in some expert ranchers to you know with the last so to
To come collect me. I always said, you know
I'm squeezing out some milk and we're having a glass of milk with me and
They turn they turn out to like me right so that happened a little bit a little bit too much for their liking right it's okay
I look like I'm not gonna be mad at anybody
Okay, not mad
because
I'm not overthinking it beat it is a horn
Well, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with, I'm not going to argue with
Faggot whatever right all these you know down to right
And all you know bait and you know what it's like Scooby-Doo is like and your plan would have succeeded if it wasn't for those damn
you know
Really know they're talking about the Scooby squad, but yeah
There are some stars some Scooby people that maybe some Scooby squads that helped me out here
that helped me realize some things, right?
And so, almost, they almost did it, they almost did it.
They almost took the passion away,
almost took the ticket down,
but things didn't go quite as planned.
Some people acted the opposite of how they thought
because they didn't quite like...
You know the people underestimate me, right? So I'm just a gay guy that knows like I'm gonna have probably insecurities that they can just poke at
I'm probably really easy just to throw off balance, right?
Somebody named Ronald Reagan that was my mod
He said that he's like, oh, it's like he's really fun to like you throw a balance
Okay, you want to throw me off balance? Okay, but you know what?
Maybe
You have to maybe to get balanced you have to know what it's like to be unbalanced and so then I can
Now I can better. I can better stay balanced
Okay
Yeah, I'm not gonna overthink it. I'm not gonna over explain
if in the future
I'll do what I'm gonna do what I want to do. Oh, it was KZ guy who was typing crazy in chat
He was trying to do it. Oh him. Oh, he thinks he's so smart. Yeah. Oh, man
I say, oh, he was that he was in a chat today
That I was in and he was demanding that I mod him. I just blocked him
I just blocked him all together from from so he I don't miss him. He also like
He was in the discord just causing a lot of problems and stuff
I don't know what he has such irrelevant information such a distraction such a distraction
Why am I every day sitting here arguing with him, right? It's like, ugh
Never again. Never again. I'm not wasting any more time sitting here arguing with the fool. I mean it could
I basically I was a fool. I was the fool, right?
Just to even entertain him entertain it, right?
A lot of people a lot of people and then it's like
Some things were set up for me to like look bad, right?
They were set up for me to look bad.
It wasn't, and it's like, and then everyone said,
oh, you betrayed your friends, you betrayed it.
I said, what did I do?
I didn't know.
I think, I don't, what did I do?
Because I kicked somebody off a panel for like a minute
or because I, or I, I modded somebody or that's the,
those are the biggest sins I think I did.
Right. Is that okay? Am I allowed to decide who I want or the mod of my type? Am I allowed to decide
How I want to run my show is my show. I mean it's my show, right?
No, it's like some people didn't want it to be much. They wanted to be
They want to be like little puppet masters and stuff like that and pull strings and pull
You know do this and you know give me that
They just didn't know that
I'm not as dumb as I look
Not as dumb as I look sometimes, right? I mean, yeah, I did some dumb things, but it's like I
Also
Have a lot of good qualities. Oh also just like total always
criticizing criticizing
Oh, you're making money like that.
And it's like, you're making money like this,
you're making money like this.
Some of them started making, doing the same thing,
the exact same thing.
I was doing, you know, the exact same things, right?
I saw the same folks, people on multiple panels
forming a campaign recruiting people to take Psyche down.
Yeah.
Yeah, some people don't know that.
And some of them are my mods, unfortunately, right?
Apollo ever see me on well Jamie Jamie
No, no, she's not he's not gonna say you he knows Jamie's Jamie's a loyal person and I Jamie
I'm in the same place as you are. I know it's not you Jamie. I know I know who it I know who they are
That's the point. It's like I saw who they are. I
Saw who they are
They're minions. They're basically flying monkeys, but it's like but not the flying monkeys. We all think right which I'm with donating
Yeah, yeah, thank you. I appreciate that. Well, yeah, it was but it's like it seemed like I
All I care about is fish tacos and dick, right?
Know well, I don't think Apollo was saying that though. They're gonna try to blame you
It's like because we're closed
They're gonna try to tear us apart and it's like I know you won't let that happen, right?
And I know you're gonna stay strong other people it was planned to
it was a planned thing to
Sabotage there's a lot of sabotage, right? A lot of sabotage
Yeah, he said, not you, Jamie.
He's weird.
Yeah, and Apollo's a good guy.
I know he's a good guy.
As soon as I figured out, like, you know, Christine.
Christine didn't like him, so I like him.
Actually, it was funny.
I was in the chat the other night,
and it was Alexander McQueen and Christine.
It was a fuck your ish, right?
And I thought and Alexander's like oh psychies betrayed me psyche betrayed me. He's the worst. Are you really shocked? Are you really shocked?
Well who betrayed who Christine? I mean it but
Did I discard anybody did I apologize to you many times and
In response what?
Telling me telling people not to donate to me
Calling me beat a stalker. She calling me beat a stalker. I
Don't stalk anybody. Okay. No, I don't need to stalk anybody. I'm busy enough and happy
My own life not to have to follow it follow anybody. I really did care for that person at one point, right?
Yes, and Jamie's very loyal, right? Yeah, exactly exactly. They're like
You know you're under it. You're under attack to Jamie and I and people will be under attack that are real ones too
And it's like unfortunately a lot of people are so
Cowardly
Yeah, but I but I but I do want to say I'm sorry to the people that did tell me the truth because a lot of people did
tell me the truth or tried to tell me the truth and
I just couldn't see everything and it's like and that maybe is like a character flaw with me
But I have been through like, you know post-traumatic stress or narcissistic views. Oh, she is what I mean
Oh, I don't know
Wow, cry me a river
You don't have to say what you did I already know I found out about me
Now there's just no chance for you and me
Baby na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
I don't think I really will care to anymore because
Did he really contribute anything to the show I remember he would sit up here and criticize me about pretty much almost you know
Right instead of pure for five hours and like not really like I don't know
What are you in what why are you here? Like there's some people that are like why why the hell are you here?
Do they sit here and like watch and throw me off balance and go go run to be that or you know go run
Guess what he said, you know, it's like an extra there, you know, oh
It's like
And then she's I don't know and it's actually gonna be very she can play innocent whatever it's okay
It's a I forget I forgive her right
She never forgave me even though I didn't do anything right she never
She's put me through more and more stuff, right? Uh-oh see you around see psychiatrists, please
Okay, I think that is oh, and you're sitting right there. What were we sitting there not saying anything, right?
Are you sitting there? Why did you didn't say hi in the chat? You didn't say how you're just sitting there waiting, right?
Go to beat is you have your VIP seat there, right?
I was like who the hell is this guy when all of a sudden, you know, he's spunky and him are fighting and stuff like that
I'm like who the hell is this guy?
And he's just like here
Always on beat is now. Well, yeah
Okay, well he might be he might be I think he basically you know
Here's a crush on Buda, I think right
He isn't BS. I mean he is yes. Yes
It's fine. It's fine. You know
Anybody can be friends with anybody they want and I don't want it's not about I'm not trying to attack her because it's like, you know
I'm not gonna go to her level
Let's just see it's very painfully obvious what's happened. Okay?
That's tricks
Um, it's painfully obvious what happened and all I'll say is not gonna happen anymore.
It's like, it's just, but you know what, I have to release.
And so with, with love, with love and thank you for everything, you know, thank you for
Unfortunately, there weren't very many positive moments there for the last, you know, six months, seven months, constant push, pull, constant changing the goalpost, constant, however, whatever energy I came with, they came with the opposite energy.
How does somebody who's not bipolar have two personalities?
It's extremely different personalities, right?
Show me my cat. Well Rudy's right here
There he is, it's Mr. Rudy
I don't know if you guys just, you guys
I'm I'm basically worse than the freaking devil if you listen to like what's been said and is even if it looks it's like
Like I'm just like
I don't know to be I mean, I don't I don't I don't want to make no no accusations and stuff
I think that is better if we like
Just kind of steer clear of making accusations, you know, if you I do have a discord and people are for you to like post
You know police reports or you know criminal records or something there, right?
Okay, well, I just don't know I mean it's like you're I don't know who you are doofy like okay
Go ahead and you're welcome to join my discord. Okay, and you can post post there if you'd like to
But I don't want to make any accusations or put a jacket on anybody because I just don't know okay
And it's like a lot of people were like
Include it were telling me about all these people. Oh guys by the way
I'm I really want to give a shout-out and
you know my sympathy to
to LD
because his his beloved
Greyhound Duke passed away, okay and
You can think what you want about him, but you know the animals are always innocent, right?
And I know he loved that dog very much
And that dog loves him and then that dog was beautiful dog and
you know, yeah his uh, so
So do you pass away that's sad
But let's hope that he went to the rainbow bridge
Okay, okay, so if you're just being ridiculous and this is not I don't want this I don't really don't want in my chat
You're just gonna be because that's you're just doing trollish behavior and it's like really here
It's I don't need to teach. I don't need people being troll or me being troll is like we already understand everybody has a capability of trolling we're here like
Connect and like
Have good energy and stuff like that. I don't want people. I don't want people attacked
I don't want people but I do want people to be just aware like, you know
Guys, I'll take responsibility for it. It's my fault. Is anything happened to my channel my fault anything that I should have
Done a better job
And I should have not let other people push me around,
pull me around so much to where I was like,
some kind of marionette and just like some kind of like,
let myself become kind of a joke and stuff like,
I'm not, I'm not, I like to be funny.
I like to make people laugh, but I don't want to be a joke.
I don't want to be just laughed at like.
Oh, he's you know, he's not talented. I mean, it's like I think I have talents, right?
Original salmon. I don't know what you did to salmon's heart, but he's deeply hurt for some weird reason. Oh, no. Oh
My gosh. Oh, I've hurt somebody's feelings
Well, you know what my feelings got hurt you my feelings got hurt you and
You know, there's also something like to be said about
There's certain people that don't really have feelings because they don't they don't they don't care about
Doing things other people hurting other people's feelings. They don't care or you know
Doxing slandering right doofy. Can you can you stop that? I'm just gonna hide you cuz I told you I don't want I just want that energy
Let's not even bring that person's name up again. He's gone. He's nice
I don't think anything man the chat. Oh, there he is. Oh, we discussing the chatter and you're bitching and there's chatters at
No, I'm doing my own show. I'm not concerned about betas anymore. Okay, I'm not gonna go run over to betas
Like you're asking me to like what she probably wants, right? No, I'm doing my own show
You know if she go ahead and you know join the cult as a member and then maybe I'll take you seriously
But it's like you're just here to like, you know beat his little flying monkey and like stuff
I'm not gonna be just pulled into I'm not I'm not falling for the okie-dokie again. Okay. This is called the okie-dok
Not falling for that
Who and you didn't go at me you're but you just sat you just sat here like
There's something up I can always tell there was something up. You're just sitting here holding your cards very close to your chest
not
Giving too much to yourself like just like not
Something not right
like who sits up here for like you know you just sit up here and you for a long time and it's like
i can say you came after me i just said what are you doing here
i do think that you might you know what i do think you might have a crush on beauty but that's okay
and i hope i hope you get what you want okay
As long as it doesn't involve like, you know
Yeah, I'm not sure I mean I mean, you know, maybe I wasn't very you know, I didn't approach you the nicest way
I don't know. I just I
Do I have all I have this is all I have is kind of just what I'm what I see. Okay. Am I feelings about it?
but I
Just have questions about it, right? It just isn't just things some things don't make sense
All I'm saying is like I'm not having open panels where it's just like people are gonna be coming up and like
I'm gonna have short shorter shows. Um, I'm gonna have
Uh, maybe more playing guests. I'm gonna have more playing material to show. I'm gonna be doing what I wanted you
I'm gonna do my readings and you know people want a reading
Okay, um
I'm like I'm saying I'm not mad
I for and it's like if you think I'm mad I'm not gonna I'm not gonna accuse anybody of anything
Okay, I've already said probably more than a more of an explanation than a shit up. Okay, so
just know I
Have there is something just I had a blinder on okay
I was letting myself be disrespected,
letting my show be disrespected,
letting my trade be disrespected.
There's people that came here, they hate my cats,
they hate me, they hate gay people,
they hate, you know, there's here to like laugh at me.
Like that's all it is.
It's like, and they got keep the matter of matter
because I was still happy or you know, still nice or.
Still had a sense of humor or something like that and they didn't want that one of me insecure. They wanted me
Just probably gone, you know, but I don't I don't give up that easy
I don't give up that easy. I'm a fighter like I said, I have if you want new into Australia bars in the first house, right?
first house of Capricorn, okay.
I'm sorry, no, it's Capricorn Aquarius.
So I have Mars on Aquarius, but my first house,
my first house is mostly Capricorn,
but the Mars was on Aquarius in the first house
at the end of it, but yeah.
I also have been studying my Vedic astrology,
and there's a lot of things in my Vedic astrology that,
Like for example, I was born under a star. It's a very rare star placement and Alexander was also born into the star
I believe called Abisha and
It means victory. It means
The conqueror means like flop, you know, it's like basically this, huh?
Like that it's victory so I'll play this song this is about my
This is about this song is about me and my birth. Hopefully you guys can hear it. I played at the beginning, but I'll play it again
Look, it's okay. It's okay. I might have
Hardly anybody in the chat anymore. Like a lot of people will get mad and like just leave, right? It's okay. I
Already lost the main the main channels already gone, right and just thousands of hours or so
I was wondering like why was why was like I not encouraged to like
Do you like make shorts from like the old shows? Why wasn't I supposed to watch that stuff?
What I just because I would figure out some stuff quicker, which I was doing right. Mm-hmm
So it's actually see the I would see the abuse again that that I had like, you know
Gone into like a dissociative state and post-traumatic stress and I was drunken and stuff over
Yeah, maybe
So here's here's my about my astrology about my astrology I can get it working
Why is this one?
Try this one.
OK, yeah, now.
So anyway, this is not even working anymore.
Here, try this.
Got it.
Oh, so what's going on?
You and ghosts with your halo dim
Airplane mode, I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is cynical
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you craved the chaos I fed
Cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I want to curse you
I could never
It's fair every wound you gave I wear we take turns being the villains
But damn it, I still want to lose not to be Celestial
But you made my pain perpetual so I did something sexual just to feel conceptual
Not to be divine, but I love you
never spoken every scar a holy mark every kiss another spot not to be divine but i love
Psychics, hell, let it read right time
Sun in my crown, that's a king reborn
Moon in my throat, every word a storm
Mars in my tongue, yeah, I cut too sharp
Make a snake show truth in the pitch black dark
Beans in my ore, yeah, they charm too real
Mercury in mine, everything I touch heals
Jupiter crowns it, and I on my face
Saturn on my heels, I was built to be great
Like, Excel, let it read right time
I don't lead sheep, I don't wake in the wolves
I don't want praise, I just meant the low rules
Mirror break, mind state, truth in the cracks
Follow my step, get your hopes so bad
I speak for the loss, for the brave
For the strange, for the ones reshaping
But the fire's all yours, I'm just a spark at the edge of the door
Psyche in the flesh, yet a stardom
I'll get in profit, try
My shadow's already half-wake on my heartbeats
Walkin' out without me, bless me, break me
Either way, I'm yours
You keep callin' it salvation, I keep callin' it a lie
I'm stretched thin in the void, perinoid halo round my mind
If I ever swore I'd rise up, that promise died under my tongue
These demons don't harm my thoughts, nah
They livin' my blood, seepin' on my back like an offering
Watching serpents on the ceiling drip
If you don't like my apocalypse
Say what your chest don't whisper it
I'm tryna be better, but the better I try
The worse I'll break
I will buy, I will out slow fate
Death and instruments I never agreed to pay
Didn't learn the lesson
Didn't learn from all the
Didn't learn from love
So give me another
Make me better
Give me another way to suffer
Made me holy in the ruin
Made to pay my
Things had all the lines Now the mirror won't look back at me
She'd fix my fractures And carve the name into my spine
Bring me till the light goes out I'm blind to every holy sign
You're the last one more around me Grab a D in human form
Touch me till I feel something Bring me till I'm finally born
And I'm drifting, drifting With the blood on the bed she's glistening
Sunlight through broken glass Like heaven wants to watch me listening to the light
Love is a curse, then I'm obsessed
Baby
I'm a place of dying slow
With the sunlight on my bed
You say you want me to stay
The forest where the outcasts sing
She walks like a flame in a serpentine ring
Emerald eyes in the hush of the night
Truth in her breath, revelation in her bite
The drums of the air
Loved Wonders of the Psychoverse
I've been wrestling with a storm of feeling
Trying to carve the right words out of the dark
You know me
I joke, I roar, I prophesy
But some truths won't sit quiet
So tonight I'm saying it plain
I don't know how not to love you
I've tried to bury it on the rituals, lifts and knee unsiduals
But it keeps rising, luminous and stubborn
You see it in my eyes when I'm near
The thicker that gives me away
You hate that you care, you hate when the tears slip
And trust me, I hate when you feel alone in here
Because even when the night gets sharp
Distance feels unreal, something in me refuses to walk away
You're perfect in your chaos, you're worth every ounce of devotion
This strange little cult can summon, and yeah, I choose you
Every damn time
But if you're riding with me, then you hear this clearly
I will carry you through the dark, not as a martyr
But as you mirror, you guide your wild eye
Brother in the labyrinth, I fight for you
Just remember
I might not leave in
And I would die for my people
Not in some tragic battle
But in the way you die for transformation
Shed an old skin to step
Into something brighter
You are worth that
Every one of you
And the distance, time, trolls, chaos, none of it shifts my devotion one inch.
I'm coming close
My beautiful misfits
The real me
I'm just a California kid with saltwater hair
A wild heart
And it's a speedo that probably should have retired in 2014
But refuses to stop believing in me
I used to laugh all night in the malibu dark
Climbing in the grass
We're sharp and complicated
Somewhere along the way
I almost forgot what it felt like
To be late
But then you showed up
And suddenly
I remember
me sometimes hard like them you really found me when you speak it's like a
private zone built out of inside jokes only this cold understands everybody
else fades all like background NPCs and it's just us
I love you, Fools.
Of course, I'm probably the biggest fool, but, right, hold on.
So why can't I just mess up the camera?
And of course, I'm probably the biggest fool, right?
But it's OK.
The fool if he continues in his folly eventually will become wise, right?
Hopefully, I'm on my way. Maybe I'm not perfect, but
thank you for your patience, guys, with me, and thank you for
believing in me. Those who do think, I mean, look.
It's just was just too negative. I want to thank that, you know, I have some really good friends
They know who they are that I do talk to
Have given me really good advice and
Saw before who I was even when I was like not very
Feeling very good about myself, you know, hi, Lenore. Lenore's kissing me kissing me
Because
I'm like we're all like we all have our our thing we all have we got we do so
for my we can all be better people or work on ourselves we don't have to like hurt
cause problems. And I mean, it's like, I've really, I don't know, can you hear me? Yeah,
I've really, I've heard some really negative stuff. Like, it's kind of like, it's like,
I just don't want to part of. So again, no shades anybody.
No offense. I'm just gonna do
I think I went north kissing me kissing me
Well, you're just oh my gosh, oh do you see home? Oh
There it is. Oh, there I am right there. Oh there. Oh, that's all
Let me see why the black
I don't know what's wrong with my camera, did I break it?
Oh my god, I did something.
Oh, maybe it's because of the band.
This thing is out.
I just want to know.
Lenore's kissing.
You're kissing me?
Kisses.
Your breath smells.
Lenore.
Kissing me.
There goes the sight of you angels, you know?
No, it's gonna be a little different. Wait 73 likes. Hey guys, do you hear me?
I just don't know what's wrong with my camera. Let me try one more time. I want to come back one more time and say hi to you
Okay, hold on
one more time
Load you hear me. Yes feel like um, I love
Oh, these cats are like, you know, there's people people people have noticed they're like there's people that hey
Oh, yeah, Nick. Hey, what's up, Nick? Yeah, we're Robin. It's kind of a new it's a new day, Nick
You know Nick has been here from beginning. I
Don't know if you're necessarily here to cause chaos or like, you know, love
But you know, I think you've been here enough and you prove that, you know
Cats love me. Yeah, and I was like it was so hurtful like you know
People it was just like that's the opposite. Oh, you know that you know, I'm
Basically, I'm abusing the cats or anything like that the cat
Like really nor can't set up my shoulder. You like to sit on my shoulder or they get you know that they were like, you know
There's complete covering in fleas. I'm like, you know, it's yeah
Mixed ogee, right? Oh
But you're my little pain. You're the panther of the coat. You're my little mini panther, right?
This linoar is a little mini. You hear a purring horn. Can you purr?
You hear a purring?
Because an OG yeah, and so yeah, you know like I was saying I'm probably gonna have less
I'm not really gonna have open panels. I'm gonna have like, you know, if somebody has something to
to talk about, and I like them and get along with them
and they're respectful.
I'm happy to have them up, but, you know,
and unfortunately, like people like,
you know, I love Alexander a lot.
He's, I mean, he gets abusive
and not only to mean to other people, and I don't want that.
And until some people can learn how to behave themselves,
at least, or just like talk like a normal person, or.
That's scream at me and you
So that I mean I have fun. I have fun with them, you know
It's hard. It's hard. There's a lot of people like that
I do like like a lot and it's like and then I thought like we were friends and
They just turn on me in a second. Yeah, we're welcome. We're welcome Nick
You know, hey Katrina, here's what I asked I asked you guys
Maybe share share my chat and the new channel with people that don't know about it
I'm gonna have to put up my another backup channel probably
You can
Upper ideas of things you'd like to learn you can ask for readings. Okay, you can
Request me making a song about you or you know something like that. You get there's like there's like actually
there's a million other things to do besides just like sit up here and and
Yeah yell at each other right
Did it get anywhere? It's just like this constant constant like negativity cycle
That gets into that it gets into people doing really bad things and I heard some right her
I heard some pretty hurtful things
Or even scary, you know the illegal thing. I just there's a lot of negativity. I don't I
Don't know if I'm
part of and I also I feel like I've been rejected by pretty much every every community and
And so I just have my own now, right? You want to hug them?
You don't have the booty. I have my own community and you know what and
I'm gonna have to act like a real cult leader in a certain way, you know, not like, you know, Charles Manson
Anything evil. I'm not trying to like control anybody. I'm trying to have like-minded people
Learn from each other, right and you can have good conversations. I
Just can't I'm gonna I don't like like last night. I came on pouring my heart out basically
People were just talking big talking that doesn't dump shit and that's like
It's not why I'm here. It's like I went here to
Have help people have fun to teach. I have a lot of things to teach. I have like I have so much to share with
I'm gonna bring up this. I have a little deck this called the deck's called
I mean I'm gonna turn on my background for a second
This deck is called making magic
We're gonna make some magic in this too, okay, we're gonna make the magic
Oh, also, I want you guys to check out the website and the website is still a work in progress, right?
But
It's getting there.
I hope that you like I'm working really hard on like
Thank you, Jada. I'm working really hard on making it cool like uh, you know
And I'm not gonna criticize other people how they run their show and they can run their shows and I hope they wish them the best
It's just like I feel like there's some bad intentions people put out and stuff like that, right?
So thank you for being here for me really there's I'm gonna be good intentions. You know, I want to welcome people
What do we have we have this power symbol?
It looks like a Reiki symbol to me called shoku rei, right? That's what it looks like. It's a power symbol
My glasses around where my trim all right
Power symbol says cleanse purify and protect the physical body, okay, how about yeah, we're not here to like
You know
Be worse. We're here. We're here. We're here to be better. We're here. We're here like, you know
You know fun, right?
but not I
don't know there's such a difference between
empaths and narcissists like, you know, some of these malignant narcissists and it's like maybe the narcissist can't help it and stuff
But it's like
I think the narcissists are better dealing it like together and then the empaths are better together and maybe like you know
Like the passing across but it seems like a lot of negativity from a lot of people who we have here
We have a philosopher stone look at the circle in a square in a triangle in a circle
Interesting a philosopher stone
Powerful manifestation of wishes and goals by harnessing universal energy. How about we all have like a positive thought and positive thoughts for each other?
You know more powerful that is into the world then
spreading a lot of
BS like a little lot of
Hate and
Some people that some people live for live for it and stuff like that. I'm used to some chaos, but
Like to create the order out of it. I like I don't like just to stay in the chaos and it's like
It's like being in a dirty pool, and it's like you just get out. It's just slimy
Right, and it's like you're not having fun swimming in it because so there's you know a piece of poop floating in it
You're like, oh need a pool with the pool guy. We have the star right the silver energy of the star brings good luck and serendipity, right?
Yeah, and also I'm really I'm not I
really want to
In my heart if anybody did have terrible intentions or hate me or anything or and or I
Just want to say
I'm gonna I forgive you okay
We have another story of mystic star right I'm born under a mystic star
It says harmony in the home and great friendships
How about that that's I'm like more like our style harmony good friendships like
We all because everyone already has problems right we don't need more problems we need more we have we need I have enough to deal with
right, I
Don't need more problems, but look at this time to shine creates the energetic
residents for golden
opportunities
okay let's take the logo a little bit
let's do a couple more of these
give the elements like I said alchemy right there's these four elements and it makes the
fifth kind of the crosses like the fifth maybe it says the elements of fire air earth and water
Yeah
Yeah, some things are hard to forgive and especially if and if I I might just have like a little like
I just have a little bit of a
Hint of some things right
Like I might I might not even have the whole the whole like you know
Might might be a lot worse than I thought it was right might be even more of a insidious
plan
but
But am I gonna sit here and be mad?
the thing do you think that is do something I just
Didn't like he was kind of like okay. He's interesting in a certain way. He's contrarian and
He's nice
There's something about him. I
Just didn't know about and he would also tell me
Don't talk about beta. I don't talk about beta like blah blah
And I don't like being told what not talk enough talk about I went down to talk about because you know, but
Then she would be talking about me and he didn't care he'd sit there. Hmm, you know, so that's what I feel like feel like
He's kind of and then he just came in here saying hey go over to beat us. She has the chatters
Do I want to be chatted at?
Like that I'm, when they beat his chat,
like I bet 100 people were saying I'm an animal abuser
and you know, I'm hurting my cats
and all this kind of stuff, right?
It's like, even if she didn't,
it's like, it's kind of by proxy.
And even if, and then I remember I did like,
I did, you know, I didn't time out anybody or anything.
I just deleted the comments,
some comments that were just slanderous.
I was told, oh, I'm hiding people in her chat.
I'm like, and everyone's up on arms.
Why am I lying right now?
About what?
Can you repeat what's the lie thing that is?
It's the lie.
You told her?
You ever say, Bita?
Why are you talking about him?
Why are you bringing the energy to?
Like, you ever say that?
You said it to me, I don't know, I'm not mad at you and maybe I'm willing to be wrong
and stuff because if you saw what I saw then you'd see that there are a lot of people that
are what happened, tell me what happened, what happened, you tell everyone what happened.
What's your perspective about it?
Maybe like you were more interested in her
Than me what what really happened something that is tell me cuz I don't know what you're referring to you
What do you mean what really happened?
Yeah, I don't know what what happened what happened was just like I woke up I woke up and I like saw things clearly right?
All I said was like I'm not mad at anybody
if you really resonate with the show
and with my energy or stuff like that,
I'm happy to have you here.
It just seems like you're more into, you know,
I mean, and it's like not like any kind of like,
you know, it's a romantic way even, right?
It's just like, it just seems like you're,
I don't know.
I have any intuition about some things.
If you keep but if you tell me what you're referring to because you're saying something happened. What happened?
So I want to know okay
We do have the lab run
Pathetic, okay, so he says pathetic see so he's not saying I asked what he's talking about
The problem is not be it itself or thing that it no, it's it's like this. It's a community
That
Thrive's on just that on unharming people on a negativity and I was specifically targeted
Okay
So and I'm not saying you're a bad person or anybody's a bad person. I'm not saying she's I'm not saying anything about anybody
I'm trying to say I don't like how I was treated and targeted and I think I from my own self-respect and
My own sanity
But I was about to quit again. I was like and I was like well why go on it's like all I go I go here. I
pour my heart out. I'm
Here and it's like
People just want to like criticize me
Not discard me
I feel so discarded. I feel so just like because it's like I didn't do anything to just discard it
like a discard is something that's like almost an abusive thing because it's like not even it's like not like
Okay, let's go our separate ways. I wish it's but it's like
Stay away from me. You you freak or you know, I was uh
If you saw how I was talking about some of these people,
I don't know, maybe you understand,
but yeah, and 90% of the people are just sheep, right?
So I'm just like, and I'm like,
I wanna be in those color coat.
I wouldn't believe.
So it says, and this is why you don't want me here anymore.
I didn't say I don't want you here anymore,
but I was like, I said, why are you here?
Okay, I said, why?
That's what I was wondering.
Because
See you're perfectly you're perfectly nice person. You're respectful on the panel and and things like that
I don't want to have you know, these long long panels anymore because
They're draining you I knew you didn't act like Alex, right?
You didn't act like ghosts who are supposedly like my you know supposed to my friends and stuff like that
But I don't think you really are
Like there's so many people that are like not into like tarot or
It's don't feel like me. I just don't I just don't know. So if you like me, that's fine. I'm happy to have you here
I'm not saying you can't be here. Did I hide you or anything?
You got maybe I didn't say it should have you know, maybe not come out and you know
said
Or it made me it made me sound like an accusation or something but
Yeah, he's he said because I don't add anything. Well
You do in your own way, I mean you have a common we can have a conversation and stuff
But it's like it feels like sometimes it's like a little bit competitive or
It's just a vibe the vibe I like you
But it's I mean I like I really do like I think everybody is sad and that's like I yeah
You didn't discard me and so I just get very suspicious because I do I did see like a lot of
People that I consider friends or that were even my mods
Kind of acting like sleeper agents
So maybe if I misjudged you I apologize, okay
Maybe you will know
If I'm wrong and I'm saying I'm not mad at anybody if somebody does something wrong forgive them. I
Just don't know
Six says W. Well, thank you. See why do you deceive people to protect yourself?
Well, can you just make how it's different the truth actually is why do you deceive people over?
Is it that I mean I was giving us actually sharing my feeling right we can have had a discussion about it, right?
but
You decided to go on and attack all of us like really like I don't think I attacked you
It's like you came at it's just a certain people that come out of nowhere. They're there and
Stunt
What so we can have we can do we can agree to disagree but see now we're sitting here arguing again
I don't want to argue it's like
just
Yeah, I'm not but I know we yeah
Guys I've apologized I think I've apologized
You know enough before I've tried to be is like I really did come in here like it's a loving spirit like and
Basically a lot of it's been beaten like I like beaten like I feel like very you know
Almost
You don't see it. I'm a lemming. Okay
Just admit you follow what people tell you and not what you see. No, no, I saw it like that
I see that's the problem was I was listening to people until today. I
Actually saw
Things okay, and not just today was I mean it is very recent, right? It's okay, but you're caught now. You're just name-calling
I'm not an animal
I'm not a, what are they, S-U-I-C-I-D-A-L little like gophers
that they're not even really like that.
The Disney just pushed them off the cliff, right?
Maybe I feel kind of pushed to the edge of a cliff sometimes.
Maybe I feel kind of like cornered and like, you know,
maybe I am a lemme, maybe they're just like
these sweet little animals that are just, you know,
Disney decided to, you know.
But they're thinking of their movie they can push off a cliff. I don't know if you know the story
But that's where the myth about lemmings just jumping off a cliff is from Disney
It's Disney film this movie where they just push them off the cliff
They just like push some okay
They didn't push them just like with their hands. They just walked right that's cute keep avoiding
Well, you're the one making these ad hominem or like, you know, what you're not really right. Let's see right now
You're attacked, you've attacked, you've attacked, attacked, right? You're making your presence known, right?
Anybody, can anybody else see that?
Tricks isn't inside right now, but does anybody else, like, can somebody else communicate with them?
I'm having a total communicating with this person.
Can anybody else give me a little bit of insight? Maybe I'm, am I totally off or what?
It's the thing that is, yeah. Well,
It says, yeah, it means calm down.
I'm coming here very even healed.
And last night, I was a little bit more upset,
but I still try to be even healed.
And it's like, I felt like people
were not taking me seriously, including you, okay?
So, but I'm willing to have a talk.
I don't know.
It's like it's like the thing is it's like I'm I don't want this conflict and so if it's just going to be conflict
It's like everyone's can go where they want to go, but I don't want to be constantly attacked. It's uncomfortable for me. I
Get enough of it
Makes me not want to continue on you should rewind the whole video where you said
Ask if I'm so welcome. You said no. Well, I said on the pan
Well on the panels. I meant that I'm not really
gonna be doing the panels as like open panels or very long panels anymore because
That's maybe like I think other people made a ruin that you know, you know, you didn't really do anything wrong, but
No
So but
But then you come in say tell the truth tell what really happened, but so tell me that what really happened
That's what I want to hear your perspective on that. I would love to I would love I mean
I
Not in vain, but I don't like to have a discussion about it, but then you just say keep going. Oh, I'm lying this and this and this
Lending and lying right
I'm not saying I don't want to be criticized at all ever
but there's a time and a place.
Okay, so, I have King Carl, how are you?
Because you said I came here telling people to look
at Beedah's chat.
You said, well, you said, you said,
why don't you go to Beedah's?
That's where the chatters are.
Did you didn't say that?
If I misread that, I apologize.
I don't know if I can still see the comment,
but I do remember, I thought that was pretty much it.
You said Beedah's live right now or something?
Or that's where the chatters are or something?
Maybe I misunderstood, sorry.
But
Okay, wait, but did you say something in the ballpark? I mean, maybe I got the quote wrong. Okay
Really, I'm willing to say gosh. Yeah, sometimes everybody makes mistakes, right?
I've been making mistakes for a long time. You said it will be disgusting the chatter that was talked about at
Me on betas. Okay. Okay. Maybe I'd misunderstood. I said, well, we talk. Oh, we'll be discussing the chatter
That was talking about me on beat it. Who's that? Who is that?
Beato what bears one? Okay, and then and you can watch
Okay, well, where when is that is that person on right now or were they on later?
It happened already. Who is it? I mean, it's just I have all these questions in my head. I'm not really, but I'm not really like
Okay, you hate all of it. Okay
Paulo, that's not very nice. Come on. I
Don't know I was just feeling like yesterday I was feeling like
Wow, I'm just not under such heavy attack. And then it's like it was especially people that I like thought were my friends
attacking me the most
I
Trust my in full not even into which I know I see I thought them so happy. Okay
The guy said you were pdf and had a prison record, okay
Well
Told them to stop saying it. Did everyone hear me say don't make those accusations. I don't want that here and I wasn't about to hide up
I mean, it's like
you know, I get called that every day too and
No
Unfortunately, I mean I told the guy I don't want that but that's what I said. Hey Paige. This is your statement
But a night or so ago when I said we can't complain and blame if we're gonna also engage in the lemming pushing behavior
You just said hurt you dear. Okay
Lemming pushing right. Oh, so you're talking to Apollo or
Who is attacking me
Who is attacking me who last night?
Because I just got called the lemming right. I just got called the lemming. He said lemming right
I didn't push him off the cliff.
Okay, I think that told me that they did get under your skin.
They do the same to you.
Yeah, I mean, I can't, I told the guy not to say it
and he's not hearing anymore.
So he says, how are you?
I mean, other than that, like I'm saying,
I don't want attacks in the room.
I think it's not something different.
It's not the comments, you don't understand.
Okay, see, well, you have to explain it correctly.
Page, I don't know, have you been here the whole time,
have a calm discussion
Yeah, I
Said I apologize if I got it wrong. I'm missing this to the thought you're talking about oh the chatter
But I did see like, you know some other stuff to happen. So I yeah, I'm sorry
We're really turning over a new leaf
That's what that's what I'm saying because I put up with stuff and like created I I took responsibility too that I've created
I'm playing most myself for most of this for being such a fool
for being such a fool and
Thinking that I could change some people people's minds about me that I you know
Do you know that there's people that just they don't they don't even like my cats. They don't like my cats
They don't or you know, they say all my cats are disgusting cover the fleas or
you know, or I abused them or
You know, these are my it's like this gets very personal, right? And then so I know you didn't say that and so I'm not saying
I'm just saying I've been that's the type of attacks. I'm talking about so that's why I am sorry if I
misjudged or
Anything my point was I'm gonna be having less of like a
free-for-all
Policy where people are calling people, you know people that I love bitches and things like that
You know or and pussy and you know and just attack and
You know all this kind of stuff. I don't like these personal attacks. Okay, and if I've engaged in some of them
Wow, I've got my cankles up because I you know, I think I have a
gotten on the defensive and I've gotten out of character and I regret that, right?
If it doesn't then then then
Don't worry about it. Then it's like it doesn't apply to you. Okay, and uh,
You know, I'm not I didn't block you from the chat or anything like that
Certainly welcome here
You've been like to have you on the panel if you're like to come on the panel ever I'm just saying
I need to do a better job of providing the content
and have more of a plan.
I need to come here and not just free for all.
I need to allow myself to be disrespected.
People saw, people I love disrespecting me.
And it's not.
Fun for me and not fun for anybody else or maybe is fun for some people
That's a problem for some people that like this chaos and like the problem like the drama and they want to cause more problems
I'm trying to cut back on that. Okay. I'm gonna say is if you did something out
You got to know how to get what's coming back to you
But what am I dishing out like so what am I just now right now?
It's not I'm saying I've made mistakes. I've but I've it's mainly been a reaction from
somebody that's
feeling abuse.
Okay?
Hi, Arthur.
Right, right, right, Paige, you can say that.
You can say that, right?
So today, right?
Is it true for them too?
Because I don't ever see that
in person getting criticized for saying shit about me.
And I've had entire panels.
Do I have entire panels about people?
Like, I'm gonna have...
I'm just a panel about hating somebody, right?
I mean, do I ever do that?
Maybe I'll say something, one negative comment.
Is that one negative comment I say?
And maybe as a hurt reaction is gonna say,
okay, well, they can just have hours and hours of stuff.
They can send people to your house.
They can send them in your,
they can send people on the door trying to open the door.
No one criticizes those people.
I mean, some people here have, you know,
but not the people I would think.
Where it's like, you know, I see people laugh about it, laugh about it, right?
I don't wanna get upset, right?
So, you know, we're being like Howard Stern just kidding. Yeah, well, it's like, you know, that was a big inspiration for my humor, but
This is, this is not Howard. I mean, this is like the panel versus beyond it where there people are
doing this doxing
about like, you know, going after
having other hosts, okay, other hosts, okay,
go after me and people that have nothing to do with anything,
right?
I mean, if you're gonna go after me, go after me.
Don't go after my pets or my family.
It's like, you know, so it's like, that goes way beyond it.
You don't even go to my driveway, which is being done, okay?
I mean, hey, Electra, how are you?
Electra's here.
Um, yeah, you know, I don't know if you're if you're kind of like
Into the party. Yeah
Panelverse means IP to combination of the community. Yeah, I don't like IP to I don't like it
I don't want to be part of it. I agree with Alexandra if I was even put on it at this point
I would ask them to take please take me off
They I found out a lot of things that I didn't know and yeah guys. I was also new to this
Okay, that's why I was willing to like
take it a lot of advice that I should have like, you know, figured out on my own, but yeah, but I didn't know it was like
as disgusting, the bad as it was. It's like, how racist, like, I mean, it's just really,
because I met Benny, Benny's not really racist, but he might have said,
it's just like this disgusting racism. I know it should be, but you know what, a lot of,
I know, and I know a lot of people are like,
Basically flying monkeys for somebody else. Okay, basically because I've seen it at work
Okay, I saw it and I'm seeing it happen to somebody else
I'm not gonna give too many I'm not gonna give me names and like or because it's like that's not what it's about
I'll just say I have a no-cis about some things that I didn't know before I have a feeling of
freedom right now of
Emotional attachment. I've there's something called fog. Okay, I've explained this fear obligation gills, right?
That's the kind of energy that I felt been very projected on to me.
Go over here.
Why don't you?
Why did you kick somebody off?
You know, how about like, if somebody else can kick off people off their panel if they
want for two minutes?
Maybe I should be able to without somebody screaming at me calling me pussy
I should be able to maybe do my tarot reading business without being called a grifter and
You know untalented and oh all these people are much better and and you know
These are supposed to my post my friend saying this stuff and it's like what did I do besides
unmod people maybe or
Kick people off the panel for a minute
It's like the reaction or or somebody else has said something and then it's like I'm accused
I'm supposed to have said it, right?
Here, here's a bottom line.
And I'm sorry if you're going to say, oh no, an AI song.
Well, you don't have to listen to it.
You don't have to be on the show.
No, I mean, nobody.
It's like no one's forced to be here.
If you don't like me, I don't know why you're here.
That's the point.
I just don't like to be laughed at.
I'm not a joke, OK?
I take myself.
my business and my
Show seriously and I always have and now I've already lost my main channel because of fucking the people
It's a tax and so it's like I have to be more strict about just having a free for all open panel
Where I just let anybody on because a lot of people I don't feel like talking to okay, but here's here's the
Just tired of holding storms you keep trying to unleash
I keep taking off my armor sometimes
But I can't carry all your memories
I haven't lost anything except my peace
You can be hurting
And if you're drowning, I'll reach my hand out and I'll sing down with you
If you wanna run from everything, I won't run from you
But I won't be swallowed by your wounds
Except my time
Trying to love someone who keeps crossing every line
I take a breath just to clear my mind
Because I can't escape when you're cutting
Press, my love.
And if you shatter, I'll hold your hand
But I won't hit the floor
If you wanna say goodbye to everything
I hope you'll find something worth fighting for
But I'm not breaking it
No one said I was a joke page.
Didn't you obviously miss it?
You obviously missed it.
A locale, a, fuck, no, dirty, flea-infested,
bedbugs-infested, just about dick, just about money,
you know, untalented, grifter, I mean,
I don't know, maybe you just weren't here
when they were saying it, but see it every day.
All I'm saying is I want some peace
and I don't want to just be participating in this hate.
I don't want to be dragged down into it anymore.
Hold on yeah
What because I wrote it guys was the AI song I wrote that bad
Like about I mean it was a kind of like a good nature. I even played on her show with her
I mean, but she talked over at the whole time, but yeah, it was you know
It was supposed to be good nature. I thought we had a relationship where I could be good nature, but no, I'm like
horrible I'm like oh this you know this was it was it that mean of a song I mean
it's like really not that song but yeah whatever the AI song was what did I
what I didn't want to say it was you know this all started over biscuits guys
it's all started over some biscuits okay and you know
Biscuits that's their favorite joke. I mean, it's like so I can't participate in the what when I say biscuit, it's wrong
But it's like that's I
Mean I just have taste the biscuit, you know, just echoing through my head into eternity now, right?
Night I even played the stupid biscuits, I don't know the time in the aggregate of a sign
It's like I like one line and it's kind of funny, but I did I have and
the other things that they're not even me like that they're
They were about like, you know, fun things.
Like, you know, you know, it's just persons with their dogs,
persons with their cat, you know,
they're all hanging out and having fun.
Maybe this person's like, you know,
calls in a little bit, a little bit drunk.
And that was kind of, you know, that was kind of funny.
You know, but I guess it's like,
I'm, I'm, I'm evil for it.
You know, I'm just like, or I deserve,
I deserve everything like negative for that.
Very few of my songs were even like this song, but there were this song
But it's kind of like you know machine on Kelly M and M can do just songs and it's kind of like fun thing
And it's like I do it whenever I do anything. It seems there's a problem with it just like
Somebody else can kick people off the panel and run their show like they want to not be criticized
I do it, I get called twisty and how dare I,
I'm hurting people that I, you know,
it's the kind of an exaggeration, I think,
for some of the people to be so upset about
some of this stuff, right?
You know what, it's always good to like,
try to see things from multiple perspectives.
And so I'm willing, I tried to, I mean, I tried to,
I tried to, I forgave so much.
Look how much I let Alexander back and look how much I like, you know, let people that have been
Really negative look how much I let's say gone. I still it's a lot. It's on the other day and still, you know always disappoints me, but right
So try I
Do have affection for people too that they don't have for me, but maybe they did pretend they did okay?
That hurts because if you really love somebody
Like that you just don't discard them and then like
Slander them and
Like slander like
Really bad like I
Told the truth about what was said
There's stuff and this people there's stuff on tape with this what we've said that is very bad
And it's like, uh, no one seems to
I don't know. It's just things with a lot of
Though it's like a double standard where it's like it's wrong when I do it and it's fine when somebody else, right?
Why?
Like and I also tried to stay in nature until I got
Don't know if you see it
Guys do you see some of the stuff that said I don't know if you can you know there's like there's people people named psyche as HIV
You know psychies, you know dead cat seconds shit cover floor and just talking in chats, you know. Oh, hi. Hi, I lied
Hi, that's that's what that's what said to them instead of like
was a spark not a throne all i ever needed was a light to call my own all i ever
that's what i'm saying age i what's wrong with my song that's what the a i song was
all i ever wanted was truth in the static a little bit of real in the world so dramatic
kept my calm mother crowd through stones
That saw me not the myth of the mass they all keep drawing the carnivals coming
But this time it's bright filled with misfits who learned to love the night
See I've been chained by my own reflection, but I burn those ropes divine insurrection now
I move clean through chaos and chatter gold from the madness. That's how come this matter
your name to bless your gift they laughed when I fell but I danced in the dirt every scar I got
just rewrote my worth all I ever wanted was to free my fear to turn my pain into something clear
now I bleed are not worried I make heaven from the mess they make we are paniverse prophets wild
and weird streaming our truth for the world to hear not broken just beautifully bent a choir of chaos
Just
The biscuit thing was used to harass me like I don't know if you like know that it was like
Person was brought up here. That's when I first even heard about it was like play that song play that song
I was like no, I can't play because the copyright play it play it play it and I kept saying play play play
I was like no, I can't play it so I didn't and then it turned into like I started being tagged in these things
And then I was like just kind of like mom. I don't know if you guys know about passive aggressive like
Chatter and like when people are referring to you not saying your name, but it's like they're referring to you
I don't know
I pick up on it because it's kind of like, it's about me, so I, I understand. Okay.
I mean, I'm not even going to play the stupid biscuits. I retired the stupid biscuit song.
There's only one line I even like, which is funny. Okay. And it is a funny line, but I want to say it
because gosh, I'll be accused of like attacking somebody. Some people's biscuits are just more
Leave them for me
It's the home
Sell by Thompson Lane
Dude look like he tried to
I stare at demon and blinked eyes wide
Mouth open spine arch like he got smited
Mid tiktok
And I don't know why this memory
Keeps biting my ankles
Why my brain insists I'm marinating
And I marinate
Wild out death is the only promise
We ever get
Yet folks treated like
Voldemort with a date
decent mortician i haven't felt a genuine emotion since pokemon gen one half my fantasies involved
surviving a zombie apocalypse armed with nothing but caffeine and poor decisions
A squirrel is just a rat with a glamour spell, me, me.
I'm a cockroach with plot armor and dream alley.
It's personally signed off on my warranty.
Office bump and he got a demon saint or cryptid.
But I still worry I'll leave a metaphysical mask behind.
And my family gets stuck with the tab.
The tab!
Who's paying the tab?
The cursor tab.
That ancient gremlin perched on the skull of ma-
Yeah, again, it's like, all my fault, right?
All I'm doing, all I did really is say,
I'm taking control of my show
and I'm gonna do what I wanna do.
And I'm not about to hate.
Why does it keep just getting thrown back at my face?
Like, I don't understand.
I'm just, see, it's kind of like,
just some people want that.
It's like, because I had enough of it.
I had enough of it.
Out of mix back that's glass job. That's maybe a little too negative
Not a bad one
See
I'm trying to be positive possible
Born on
But I'll shout the way the quiet become kings
Where victories come slow, but when they land they stick like rings
Sagurizing with the grin
Oh, 32, I'm sorry, it's too low
Po
Oh my gosh
I don't think I put the wrong place
Bear with me, I'm sorry
Look what I have. Do you guys like leftovers?
But they're fish tacos. They're fish tacos actually. See I mixed on myself.
I'm the fish tacos beetle guy, okay?
Stick with that.
Let me know if there's anything else you'd like to adjust or create.
Yeah, exactly. Thank you. Thank you. I will let you know
Okay, here we go
Sagurizing with the grin like you've already seen the map
Dropping truth, dressed up in jokes, pulling futures out of the gap
Moon cold and Capricorn steady as a cobblestone face
Turning heartbreak into power, pacing yourself like it's a race
Put a panel on the mountain, let the thunder speak your name
You're the undefeated one, whoo-whoo-whoo
Climbing with the moon still young, whoo-whoo-whoo
Every loss becomes a run, whoo-whoo-whoo
On a ladder that nobody else can see
Enjoy the rises from the red turning shadows in the scripture turning chaos into checks by Lava
In your footsteps new beginnings in your stride every fall becomes a launch pad every setback is your guide
You gather tribes like magnets gather filings in the dust you speaking people love it's something ancient in the trust
You got that cold leader energy without the poison in the cup you lift the vibe name the darkness tell the whole
But your steady capricorn moon turns every rumor into fuel
You walk forward, come and show
Truth behind you like a cure
You're a storm that God's designed to take your time and change the world
in the dark
Well, that was, I'm sorry, thank you.
Thank you for just, you know, listening.
Yeah, let's say, let's see, craters be creeping
and crawling in the night, just autistic ones with fur.
What does that mean?
Like, what's that referring to?
Squirrels?
Like, again.
I love uh, I love uh
Jokes, I just don't like being the joke
Gosh
Hi
Anyways, I know it's gonna get worse before it gets better because people are not gonna like
Me standing up for myself because I'm expected to like
Lay down
Take it nope
A glitch in the cathedral
Flash rebooted from the static
Memory dripping down the altar of my tongue
Now a lawyer's here, no counsel, only
She
Is it safe?
What?
Thank you, Gotti, thank you.
Okay, well, I know you guys are getting sick of me, right?
So, I'll play one more and then I'll stop music, okay?
I just wanna play one more.
It's so good.
There's a hum under the poles, a secret code in the river's tone
A metropolis of mirrors, built on ruin and data blood
Upon the spout of seven rides, their heads crowned with hunger
Their tongues forked in prophecy, and she, the queen of noise
Sit strapped in stolen light, until the truth undresses her bed
I'm a dealer's a signal
I've seen hell
I'm gonna stop, I'm gonna stop for that at least.
Where am I?
Oh, here.
Over here.
There's an oil, I think it, right here, yeah.
This is actually, it's from a Pooja kit.
But I don't know exactly what everything I'm still learning.
You know, Pooja.
I know this is like a Sarah spotty
Sorry my nail my nails, I'm sorry
Do you have a crush on CB Gotti? I want to know right now
I know now
Okay, but look guys, I'm working on like stuff like that look the cookie cool is
It's my I can be one of my screens and we kind of also like a back screen like this
Um, but it looks like this, I think
Similar to that, okay
Working on nice graphics. I'm trying to get the show better. Try my best
You guys want from me. Oh, there it is. You can see it
You know the nor the nor recorded a message for the
The cult
She did
You know didn't work and talk she can
You would just listen she talks
Hey Rudy hi babe hi mr. Root
Garden of broken gods we plant our screens like seeds out of pixels prayer grows
We call it a cult, but it's really a communion between the wound and the one who tens it
We are gathered in the glow of screens our rosaries made of emojis our hymns corrupted files
Yet still we rise singing through distortion the cult of psyche burns in the bandwidth
Yep
Pretty amazing
Absolutely amazing. Hey Rudy, you guys want to see Rudy? Look at Rudy is so old. You're a little old man
You're a little old man, rude
How are you?
Rudy likes to spend all the time sitting on the couch now with me. You do
You're getting old you're like an old you're a little old man
You like to sleep on the couch and when I fall asleep you come and lay on top of me and then you fight with tricks a little bit because
And then Lola's mean a little bit
She's sleeping. Don't worry tricks. It's a cool cool cat, you know
Lucky to have such a awesome cat and also guys. I'm lucky to have you guys too because you know what I
Just be sitting here alone
And sometimes even like, you know people being mean to me
It's better than being alone sometimes, right? I have to be like too like
sounds stupid or whatever but I appreciate you and I do love I mean I
can't really I try to like say I hate you know I want to hate I can't really I
can only hate the behavior right and maybe I hate my own behavior too
sometimes but you know what we're imperfect people but also I've been cast
every show almost and every, you know, so many people, you know,
not wanting me to be part of it, like, but, you know,
that I'm for the outcast.
So it's like, why don't I start my own group
and then anybody can come here.
And it's like, I'll accept, I'll accept anybody pretty much
as long as like, you know, they're not like attacking me.
Constantly or trolls or like, I mean, you know, not not troll but it's like trolling me
Trying to irritate me, you know, I saw this guy Ronald. His name is Ronald Reagan
You know what he said? He said oh
In a chat just like with that. It's been mods in there
Oh
Thank you so fun to throw off balance. Isn't it fun watching go off balance and like, you know
getting upset and you know getting me trying to like you know desperately to get peace because
I'm about peace but right if you think I was I can't even mean sometimes I'm trying to make people
laugh I'm trying and it's like sometimes um you know
We can have a good-natured lab. I mean, it's like I certainly things are not always said in a good-natured way toward me
They've said and I'm really cruel way a lot of the time, right? I still reach her. I still try to say
Hey, let's be creative and like, you know, we can at least make a art form out of
kind of
so kind of
You know
Joke right
You're gonna you're gonna troll like that, you know, let's just just be like fun trolls, okay?
So, what do I have here?
Yeah, so hence, ooh, this looks good.
I can just watch that a little bit later, but yeah.
So hence, something like this.
And you know what?
This may be out of someone else, but you know how much I relate to this song?
You know made a few different choices in my life, right? Hold on. This would be me right here
Check this out
It looks like me too and I want to play this part in the musical, okay
like shining true just rolling fast they know my
I know that one problem is probably the shoddy
Let's smile again
When I feel like murder again
I'm in love with fish, not screaming fish
I've been reaching someone's out, but it ain't me
I'm in love with fish
They call me Chris, but they don't...
This guy is going to be the pilot again
When I feel like murder, okay?
I have a vision so I'm going to get his feet
Maybe he's going to be the clever man
face to black
I still whispered
dish come back
Is there anything like that mean about that?
I don't think it was that mean.
Dirty nipples, I can't play that one.
That's not my song, okay?
But it's a good song.
Why don't you take your wrench away, Arthur?
I'm painfully embarrassing.
Who is?
Can I get an explanation why you're right?
Oh, come on, Arthur.
I'm your liar, I never said it was fun to watch.
Hold on.
Never said it was fun to watch you decline
You are no better than beta and one and the same a pair of liars reason and you're turning on me only supported you
But you're better than the rest of these delusions. Oh, you're no better than the rest of these delusional weirdos. Oh my gosh
You know who kind of did laugh at the song in a blogger, but that it looks more like me than blogger
You know, you gotta admit and I really like that song. I
Mean it's like I really do
except for like, you know, the wine mommies and like the
The 5150 part but most most of it, you know
Resonate with
That meat was that bad. I think it was pretty funny
That's actually based on the growing theme seems theme song and I actually was the one that said put in the line
Show me that smile again
Arthur
If you want your wrench, join the cult.
And then I'll consider it.
But I need dedicated cult members to have wrenches,
not just like everybody, right?
It kind of like makes the wrenches lose their meaning.
Plus you insulted me several times
and I don't think that my mods should be insulting me
on the, no, on my own stream, but, you know.
Is that is a wrench really that important? I don't like a wrench because it's like wow all of a sudden
You know I have responsibility, I would like to have like mods that
Are like proactive for me and stuff. I don't know, you know, I took away everyone's wrench practically. I'm giving I gave some back, right?
Especially to people that have been really supportive of me and it's my way of saying thank you to them, too
It's because they mainly treated like an honorary thing anyway
But you know I will consider you for one. It's like what why you're bitching about a rent?
I took I took everyone's wrench away because
Like no one's using it, you know, I have people
Doxing and stuff like that and then nobody's taking taking I'm hiding the comments or anything
And so it's like I need to have like a mod meeting and stuff. So I have people. Oh
Look at look at house house hour. How old is this? Yeah? What do you mean?
Yeah. Hey, Archie. Is that a giant bed behind me? This is my couch
See coach
Ouch, I'm in a giant bed, it's just a couch.
There's my green screen, that's the kitchen, table.
Maybe you want to see my TV?
You can see, watch yourself on TV, look.
So I'm looking at, see, it looks crazy, it looks crazy.
It looks crazy, it's why I look crazy.
Yes, so let me see. Okay. Go ahead. Go ahead guys now troll me. Tell me how you can just go ahead and troll me
Well, there's no point in giving you a wrench if you're not gonna show loyalty, right? I do this shit every month you've had it
It's my show I can I can give and take away wrenches
That's one of the benefits of having a show I can give away wrenches as I see fit
If I want to and I don't have to be bulleted to giving one to anybody
You know, I don't need to like
Give be giving one to people that are talking on my back and other chats
Making fun of me and other chats not ever defending me and then it's like if I say well, can you like me maybe say?
Hey, well, I know psyche and he's like not
You know fucking you know Satan and you know Satan's
Tony L reincarnated right so
Right, but no, we're sitting in our comforts participating at the time so
What what what are you talking about? No, I'm no Apollo. I'm not and you have to keep yours
I don't want him to have it. You can you better guard that runs with your life
You're in the peanut gallery watching Berry kung fu master. Okay good
I'm going through man up pause
No, I'm not I'm not 50 years old yet. I was kidding. Oh, coach. Co is not crazy. Okay. Thank you. We'll be saved
Yeah
No, Paulie, Paulie, you have to follow you have to you have to have the rent and you have to be a good mod
Or else I'm gonna give you another wrench imagine having two you think one is bad think about the responsibility there two wrenches Wow
I don't really talk about Arthur. What what money are you talking about? Like and plus it's like, you know, I'm this show basically
I'm not monetized and so
What money
Understand
We're engaging in right there is financial trolling acting like there would be some money
But I'm never going to defend you anywhere ever again. I won't add to it
But the rest assured you will not be defend. Are you blogger?
Are you blogger the reasoning?
Come on because what did I do besides besides play that song?
I didn't what what did I just did like why are you why all of a sudden you're mad because you're in that you're
Being all nice. Oh, so maybe you're just being fake
Yeah, I'm used to that
Not blogger people. Why are you being fake them? Why are you being nice when you came in?
I didn't say anything at all to you, right?
Same your reasoning. Well, then you're just a mature guys and it's like I need I need my mods to be kind of mature
I need and it's like I need to have like kind of like I
Lied on you how tell me
We won't even get wrenched at betas because we are not females, obviously.
She has two, she has males modded.
You're Ronald Reagan, Ass Clown.
Oh, I ran Ronald Reagan. I saw you in another chat.
And what did you say, Ronald Reagan, Ass Clown?
You said, isn't it fun to get psyche off balance?
So, right?
It's funny to throw me off balance.
And so you're just trolling, okay?
Caught, you got caught.
Sorry.
Baby
It's not true. Well, I saw your name on the screen and bloggers chat saying that so and I was told
Hey, watch out for this Ronald Reagan guy. There you are. You rebuild yourself. You were a mod. You were a mod
The Ronald. Oh, I'm a liar now. Sure. I
Must have been seriously for me. I don't even know how you got the wrench the first I must have been fucking out of my gourd
Okay, insane
Must have been insane
I'm banned. Yeah, yeah, he's banned. Thank you Carl. I think I'm like, Carl's I'm warming up to Carl
I think I'm warming up to Carl Carl. You warming up to me yet?
Might consider modding you if you want
I am a mini beta. Oh, yeah, I've gone too far
No, I'm sorry, I won't do my voice game
Mini be you know who else like you know who else is annoying. I'm KZ. He came following me into some chat
Who just bothering the annoying the whole chat, you know, I
Don't know. It's just an annoying person. I had you modded before I know I'll mod you again
I mean I am modded everybody pretty much today, and I was like gonna start fresh
Just based on like how people were acting and
Then some people are acting out and proving that they wouldn't be appropriate mods and they're modding with their fifis
I know Casey is I know he was just he was annoying everybody and like
In the chat and following me around something like demanding. I've mod him and so I was like
No Casey
And he posted some stuff on my discord like of his
Excuse me like look at my teeth are nice and he's like posting his bone bills and stuff like stop hosting this shit
No, we care. Yeah
Okay guys, well, let's see I'm kind of like making my point it's like
I'm cool. Okay. You're cool with me. I thought you were kind of like where you're teasing me a little when my channel not taking that
I think you were like the first person you're like, I got your channel taking them. I don't think you did. I
Don't think he really
care that much about
Your numbers are in I really know what
And if you really like me, you'll want me to be happy first of all and like continue to be like
When did you come on and stuff and you know, you'll want to keep my channel going and stuff, right?
It's not make sense. I don't know if you don't
Not really good not that loyal to anyone because you go everywhere. Well, you can go everywhere, but I'm saying like
Some people just go and sit on panels where they're just right about me and stuff. Is that a gold snake?
Yes, this is a was the staff. Yeah, it's a beautiful cobra head of the right
Um, King Carl, you're not asking I know you're not asking you know why because you're not asking for mod
That's what I'll give you much and I'll make you an honorary member of the cults. Okay
Yeah, and it should be it should be it's okay, like, you know, it's okay to like go go to other chats and stuff like that
For a mod I'd rather I would rather have
my mods at least
Throw in a kind word or something like that, right? Thank you
So it's like you don't have to like
Go against it or like make yourself stand out. I mean at least just just don't say anything
but I straight out have people participating and
You know in the kind of like the atmosphere of it, and they don't think very much of me
Why do I want to be disrespected by my own mods?
Does it make a sense or are you gonna have if you had a channel would you have?
Mods that went out and disrespected you
Right
Okay, yeah, I don't
Like so it's like so I love to bring on conquer by talking about a vegan patriot and peps. They're your concubines. Oh my gosh
Well being patriots. Hold on
Did you know I have a secret identity
I am the real vegan patriot, guys.
Did you know that?
I am the real vegan patriot.
You stood up for me, well I didn't see that,
you should've clipped it and let me know.
No one else did?
Oh, I didn't really see.
I mean, you were kinda like.
You stood up for a lot. Okay. We'll clip it. I had better channel only psyche could be mod. Oh, and you could
Block the haters before they even typed perfect. Thank you. I love that won't be safe. You should start a channel
Yeah, Arthur what yeah, you are I know you're on panel with me, but what do you say on panel?
You're like, oh, don't play your stupid AI song. Oh, and then you were like saying other stuff, right?
Kate got mad at you. Well, you know Kate
She did you so you're on Kate's doing it. Yeah, I mean, I heard I heard I just don't want to like listen to these rumors
But I did I did I was told does anybody know who VB is it's BB a
Trustworthy person
source
because VB told me something yesterday that was very shocking about
Kate and
Gish
But I won't even repeat what she said, but we get great. Yeah. Thank you
No, I feel pretty I feel pretty in it, you know, I
Said Ali stop fucking with psyche and everyone should stop allowing Alan on piano
Well, I do appreciate that Arthur. Yeah, I'll put you in now. You just got you just gained a point, right? You stood up for me. Well, good. I
appreciate that okay, and if you and
I'm not saying
You won't have your wrench again, but I'm saying
Give me a minute. I'm not having my you know
And don't badger me for it. It's not something like it's like it's like it's like a
You know, it's a little honorary thing sometimes, right? You really like to wrench this though, right? I mean, it's like
I mean, it's not even that big of a deal, but
And also, oh, whatever do you see so whatever so it's whatever then it's like whatever
Don't don't defend me, you know, but but
Did I mean did it work?
That would be really hey, what's up? What's up, Alexandra? I might wake up. How are you? Oh, yeah, I'm so I
Did I'm not everybody
Sweet heart I played I've been playing I played that I love the vlogger
Music video so funny
But I said, you know, if I made a few different decisions in life, I might, I mean, I kind
of relate to the video a little bit scarily, you know, except I'm a little bit, like, a
bit taller, right?
Yeah.
Good to see you.
Really?
Yeah.
Well.
Yeah, I was at Trish's today and and then I was I saw your you had a great like live the other day
It's so funny
I'm really enjoying just hanging out watching that and everyone make sure you subscribe to ip2 wiki.info
and
I just want to really also thank you alexander because
When I felt like nobody got me or like, you know, I was just like a joke and it's like
I wasn't getting very much positive feedback and I was kind of like
It's kind of lost you know you
were like
You're like I see something you're like I see something in you and you you know
That really gave me hope and also you
shared a lot of a
Lot of your thoughts on some things with me that it took a little bit to sink in
But when it did wow lightning. Yeah, Trisha was good. Yeah, that was great to them. I
Enjoyed it a lot and wow it was really also cathartic because
You know, I'm feeling kind of dumb
I'm feeling kind of oh hi Lenore. I'm feeling a little bit dumb and I kind of like you know that
First of all, I fall for the love bomb like by that right certain person and
Second that I didn't
See what was going on sooner because today a lot was revealed, right a lot was revealed of
How things are really working behind the scene or maybe behind the scenes
And I'm seeing my I'm seeing myself what I'm seeing
I'm seeing whatever, things that happened to me,
I'm seeing happen to, I don't know, it's just like, wow.
I'm a little bit, I feel a little bit lighter.
I'm kind of, it's kind of like you carry around
like a big heavy backpack or something like that
and then you take it off and it's like, I'm still like,
oh, I'm free, I can move, I can like do it, I can do it,
I can like, I can.
No
And also, but also it was cathartic because she his trisha like revealed like she had been through very similar
Things you know and maybe with it, you know the opposite sex, but right so we can relate and it's like almost like
We're able to
Is ghost loyal ghost the other day?
started saying
Tell me what not to talk about and talk about my show I don't really want to be told
What to talk about not talk about I could talk about anything I want and and so
He might be my mad at me because I stood up for myself and I'm like
You know what if you have your own panel you can decide the topic of it and you can decide what to talk about
but
And I you know I love ghosts and stuff like that he
Gets a little bit wild sometimes
Hope I hope we can help you get we'll make up, but you know, I
Just can't be bossed around right?
Hi, baby. Oh my god. No, I'm kissing
Kissing are you happy you love me?
People say oh
There's poor cats this poor cat. You love me. Oh, no, you're kissing my face
Well, oh, no, I'm sorry
Me kisses you give me kisses
You're a good cat. You're the sweetest cat. She's so sweet.
My little kitty cat, my little plant, my little black canther.
Oh! You love me?
I was like, remember I was, I was like, it's the almost crying one time and I was like,
because I had another black cat and the cat kind of ran away.
And I was crying. I was like, I was like, the cats are the only
beings that I don't feel judged by and then
And so my friend like arranged to get Lenore. She she like asked my friend to find a black cat
And then my friends too she's a she was a cat rescuer
And she like saw this little black cat running around inside her work
She put a little trap out some food in it and then she came out at lunch and
Thank you. Thank you. I'm feeling better, but I know it's gonna be like a little bit
There's gonna be some some some pushback about it because people are used to me being one way and it's like
But I was like, you know, I've already lost a main channel and then all you know
already feel kind of under attack here and
I've had a couple friends just like
Kind of like go off on me, you know, and for like
You know, I would kind of hurt and I was like, you know what I
want to
I want to be like a better
Positive force. I want to have better content. I'll be on I probably will be on less. I'll probably have less panels
You know, if I if I want to have somebody up and talk it's like I will but
I've had this like open
free-for-all kind of thing and
And people kind of, I think people kind of take me
for granted a little bit sometime
and don't necessarily think about the person
that's like, you know, or like any of the sacrifices
I make and everything it's like I do is wrong.
And so I just have to stand strong in myself, right?
So thank you, I just, and I love you.
Thank you so much.
I'm just a Miss Lenore. Lenore your sweetheart, and I'm not choking my cat. See I'm holding her by the
Airfront next right there. I got this. Thank you, and I have like like I said I have
There are there is like a circle around that basically hates me. They hate they don't like the cats
They don't like me. They don't like tarot. They don't like my any beliefs. They don't like my
music idea or
Anything about me. They mean the course against a one nice thing and so there's a group of like that around me
But there's a there's another group and it's even closer
It's it because it's smaller so it's gonna be it's good. So it was and that group that group is surrounding me, too
and they they're showing me with love and and and really good advice and
My my my friends keep me going, you know, you love that keep her in keep her
You hear you pur
She's purring
Yeah, I'm think I'm in a much better state, you know
I'm not like and I'm I wouldn't even mention names, but I do have this haters exposed deck
And so I can pull a few more cards of these I did pull a few cards earlier and I do the resonated when I was playing earlier
This one says
spreading rumors about me, okay
And these might you guys relate to any of these two like are you having rumors spread about you?
I mean this community is kind of kind of can be brutal, right? This one says
Hate tweets towards you pretty bird tweet tweet, okay?
I don't know if it's necessarily on Twitter,
but, and this one says causing you to miss out
and miss out on an opportunity.
You know, do you think that people saying don't donate
to him or people saying he's a grifter and don't do terror?
Do you think that could cause people to say,
well, I don't want to go to him, right?
It's like a bunch of people are saying it,
like almost in a campaign.
Today that Apollo did verify there are groups. He's seen talking about taking me down, right campaigns
He's look like I have actually have a labyrinth deck somewhere in my room. I'm gonna get that later
Let's pull a few more of these just see if there's any
Screw the haters. Let's get high and drunk and laugh. Let's do it
Look at this. This is this one says blocked heart chakra
Issues and tensions affection balance between beauty compassion and empathy healing love
Mindfulness and nurturing relationships. So maybe some people's have a heart. I have a blocked heart chakra, you know
and
Because you have to be kind of heartless to like want to hurt somebody like really hurt somebody like if I ever was
Troll it was a good nature. It was not to like cause a person to cry or
to like
You know, basically, thank you. Thank you, Alexandra. I love you. Thank you. I feel it. I feel it. Thank you
Just thank you for just being you I
Think you're amazing amazing amazing woman and really I think
You're you're one of the main reasons I woke up and it's like or I could
Because it's like it's been months and months and months of like the same thing of like this
Me trying to like walk on eggshells and like maybe what can I do to like fix it fix it fix it fix it fix it
You know trying everything I can and then it's like and the goalposts keep moving the personality keeps changing the
And then it's like what's going on and it's like okay now. I see now. I see there's there's
I meant very clearly because yesterday I felt like the demon or like the curse or the spell or whatever it is
I felt it come off yesterday. It felt like something being pulled off my neck. That was like biting on real tight
Okay, and then I was like the then it's like whoa
Well, it feels down feels like weird because it's missing because it was been there for a while, right and then
today I
Saw things that were like
Like the lights
I get it. I get it now. I get it. Why? Why did I allow that?
Probably my own attachments, right?
Why did I allow that?
There's something called an empath and a narcissist dynamic sometimes
where the empath is desperately trying to get the narcissist to
See them or to you know to forgive them or something and then the artist says we'll never
Well, let's keep moving the goalpost around and never never like never let it happen
Or they might let it happen for a second and then it's like it's like it goes on a cycle
And then it ultimately discard and you know, I'm gonna stand up for the people that are discarded
Because a discard is just different than breaking up, you know, you can like say
Hey, you know, you know, maybe we're not right for each other's lives
But there's like sometimes people are just dangling this little
They're just dangling the same like oh here catch get this carrot
You can never catch the carrot, but it's always gonna be in front of your face
They're just walking around right so I felt sometimes I
know I was
Pretty pretty dumb I
Feel a little bit dumb, but you know what I posted a quote today that says a
Fool if he's to persist in his folly becomes wise and I definitely
It was persisting in that folly, right? But you know what? It did bring me wisdom finally and I would also say
Some prayer and connection with like the higher powers and things like that
were helped to orchestrate things in divine timing and so
Thank you to the universe
This one says they can't stand to see you shine, right?
Look, I can't help it. I just shine, but you know what I want I want other people to shine too
Yeah, yeah
At least I did at least I did end up
Getting it and it's like because it's like I've come very close. I've had I've had some of these understand
But I always was kind of like
hoping for like peace or friendship or something or like,
you know, basically it's acceptance,
it's the acceptance and it's like,
like I said, and now I'm learning,
I don't need to be accepted by everybody, right?
Part of my journey is not being accepted.
So maybe I could be the person that is accepting
of people that aren't accepted.
So I don't know if you guys have seen.
Like the green woman, I'll play this quick video. I don't know if you've seen this
This is the green woman is she's like she's a goddess of outcasts. Okay
She's also the goddess of like speech and art her name is Matangi. I made this video today
Check it out
In the shadows of the forest where the outcasts sing
She walks like a flame in a serpentine ring
Emerald eyes in the hush of the night
Truth in her breath, revelation in her bite
The drums of the exiles thrum under her feet
Downbends words, twists, time loops, repeats
She lives having a made of shattered green glass
Strings of your memories, your future, your future
Oh
She's also the goddess of leftovers. I like I love leftovers. I always did. I'd love leftovers and like I made this a little like a thumb clip
This is this is like reading fish tacos for leftovers
Yeah, and I do plan to do some um, you know present a presentation, right?
and let you learn more about her
because the Mahavidyas are very extremely interesting.
My hair color.
Yeah.
But yeah, she represents this like divine speech
and you know, Tantra and I love her beautiful green skin.
It's like you have to find what inspires you so if you know, maybe I
Actually feel very called to certain people are certain
Like you know, I don't reason
Sometimes when you feel called, right?
Like they are calling you
What is make a million make a million and you go first. Oh my gosh guys
I'm gonna make two million dollars tonight. That'd be so awesome and that'd be cool
If I do, I'm gonna
Send it very wisely
No, I don't I don't think that it's okay. It's okay. You know I
I know I get accused of just being
interested in fish taco and dick
but
I'm actually
Here for like a bigger purpose, I think
Or else I wouldn't bother with
Because wow, I can go to the Salvation Army and you know
Okay, you don't have to fight about doing anything it's really you know, I appreciate I appreciate anybody that donates it does
Go into the show production. I do spend a lot I'm trying to build this website. It's gonna be so cool. I
Do have like a lot of progress. I'm making on it. I can show you
This is this website. It's called cult of psyche calm, but if it's a K, right? K u l t
I've been working on it for over about two months almost
It is looking
And feeling I want it to I'll show you how it looks
Can you let me know?
If you think that this is any good
Okay
And so yeah mission
There are
Principles
There's different ways to like there's made my Etsy store. There's discord link there. There's other things
mailing list
There's different portals
Let me see if some some pages might not work, but yeah, I think I'm doing a good job on it. It's looking pretty cool
See, let me see and you can also there's like a token system that let's see the fish taco revelation the prophecy explained
Right you can hear the full fish taco prophecy right part of the lore
What does this say? It says in the beginning there was hunger not for food, but for meaning and in that hunger the universe delivered a fish taco
This is not metaphor. This is the literal truth of how consciousness awakens to itself through the most mundane and experiences
The fish taco prophecy teaches us that enlightenment does not arrive on a mountaintop
It arrives at 2 a.m. In a parking lot wrapped in foil absolutely perfect in its imperfection
Okay
These are the beginning teachings and so yeah, so why cats are enlightened cats do not meditate
They do not read of self-help books and yet they are more enlightened than 99% of humans
Why they live in the present. They have no ego. They embrace paradox. They demand nothing and expect everything
The cult teaches us stop trying so hard. You're already enlightened. You just forgot also be the cat the cat is always hungry
Also, you know, I'm like nine so a lot of I have some of my my numbers my numbers are seven and nine, right?
Born on the seventh and then my life path is nine
And so there's nine levels to cult, right?
There's a membership you can join the cult
These two higher levels will have like a telephone call a 30 minute call 15 minute call talk about anything you want get a reading
I do plan on having some really cool merchandise, especially I want to do some, like, some books.
I want to do some, like, maybe Leatherbound, very limited edition books and other things, right?
There's a lot, there's a lot to it, there's either, there's gonna be, you know...
Have the Discord also running better.
There's gonna be members only nights.
Also, you can also, if I ever disappear again,
look, you can go to,
let's see, where is it?
Live, right there.
And look, I'm live on kick.
And stream, you can even chat from my website
onto kick right there, okay?
And I'm gonna have a schedule more updated, stream etiquette.
There's also my links to everything.
You know what guys there's even oh, yeah, I just want to show you guys, you know, if you don't want to like, you know
If you'd like to go in the free the free route, it's free open the gates you get access to the live stream open panels
You get to talk in the chat you can earn these like
Sigils, you know, I custom design sigils
entry-level prophecy pulls during a stream and then occasionally you can
Members only pull, you know, you'll be shouted out sometimes.
I mean, that's for free, actually, that's free.
What a great deal, you know?
And then everything there, if there's gonna be,
I'm still working on all the benefits,
but there will be benefits.
And there's this whole table explaining all the benefits.
FAQ, I do plan to do the panel verse on this, you know?
I still have a few things to do still,
but then there's also a members only section.
There's also,
Easter eggs, okay, there's like things that you can find that you might
Yeah, you won't see they're like little secrets on the website
And I only I won't even give any away because they're just surprises
But you have to be there like if you're on the website at certain times
They might show up if you click the certain place if you like go in a certain there's stick those little hidden surprises and
Guys, there's a whole
Talk about a like a lore this I think you know, this is gonna be hotter than Scientology. I think my religion psych
Psychotheonism is my religion. Okay, so anyway, please check out cult of psyche.com. I hope you know
if I'm trying to get everything working perfectly, but
Hey, I'm on my way. Okay on my way. I think it looks pretty cool
There's a discord
Yeah, you can dumpster dive for the points. You want a Lenore shirt?
Yeah, and I'm gonna have like the I'm turning into a fish taco shirt
I'm gonna have the go hate yourself or go hate. Yeah, go hate yourself shirt from the psyche haters club
You like the you like the points. Yeah
Yeah, I mean the point is like you can just earn them just by referring people to the site or by there's like
Oh, I think it's there a little quiz too. I think there might be I think I don't have the quizzes up there
Because you can take I can take the quiz and then it will assign you like a you know a kind of a role
Also, there's this for rules available to
Remember it's KULT of PSYCHE
It's the link is in the my channel description. I don't know why this. Okay. Yeah. Do I have
the quiz up? Let me see. I might not have it up. Let me just look at it. Yeah. So there's
there's different uh exercises and rituals uh there's this doctrine page but these universal laws
let me see psychetheanism um origins or i need to yeah i think that the um some of this stuff was
kind of resource intensive and so i'm still working on getting everything perfect okay but
you know what we're getting there we're getting there humor
Prophecy teachings
Okay, let me see anything else I can share resources, what's that?
Okay, yeah, there's just cool stuff guys. I'm working really hard on it
Okay, like and I do hope you I do hope you check it out, okay
So let's see what's going on in chat
Who
Guys come on. No, are you guys fighting in chat? Don't fight about it's okay. Don't fight about
Don't fight about uh, you know, don't fight over me
It's like you want me to dumpster dive for the points like I can do that
Yeah
Get the points. Yeah
Yeah, so
I think you guys will like it
Do you remember? Yeah, so, um, I
Do want to say
Thank you guys tonight. We're pretty good better than I thought I thought maybe people would be a little bit
But I think people are understanding like I want to be here as much as I can for you guys. I do love you guys
Really, I do
I'm here basically because I love the people if I didn't have people talking to me or
I'd be very I wouldn't really be like streaming very much, but
Make it fun for me. Okay. I love you
You'll play a song and then let you guys go
And maybe I'll be back later, but maybe I should
Take some time to work more on this on everything, okay, but let's do a fun song
I'm here
Yeah, I mean I love that song I played it earlier. Yeah, please say I haven't played
Trixie.
with super chat pricing
Thank you very much!
So, before I go, though, I want to do a reading if anyone wants one, and, of course, happy
to do a reading for anybody, for some, thank you, yes, and, like, you know, I do like to
Nice long one anyone wants to yeah, you like one Jamie. Okay. Let me get a bit. That's these very cars first
some very cards for
Some very cartoons Jamie James
Okay
They're called fairy dust I
Guess there's a lot of smoke. Oh, I don't know if you saw this this is pretty funny
You guys see that smoke? Let's see. Do I have that?
Well, I did have something where she's some smoke. You know what smoke?
And then okay, yeah right here look. Oh shit, I'll have to do it again. One second.
Wow, look, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, logger size.
I'm just kidding.
Okay, let's go, Jamie.
Okay.
Put Jamie James, Jamie James.
Arrows, we have arrows.
It says, direction.
is yours to choose today.
Your inner light will guide the way, okay?
Direction is yours to choose today.
Remember, we can just say, you know, shoot these arrows
and direct them to our destination ourselves, okay?
Direction, it's in your hands, you get to point,
you get to choose the direction, right?
We have practice.
After a while,
you'll dance on air.
Practice makes perfect, you're almost there, okay?
You're practicing something and improving, okay?
What else we got? We have family
Yeah
Says whatever wherever you go
Whatever you do your family is here for you, okay?
That includes us okay, oh we have animal healing
It says, no matter the creature, earth, sky, or sea,
animals show how true love can be.
Speaking of animals, I do want to send condolences to LD.
If you ever saw his, he has a beautiful greyhound named Duke
and Duke passed away last night, I think.
Yeah, last, and so, no.
Love that dog that dog loves him that I was a happy dog my dog was a good dog
Flowers flowers will brighten your space and create a very friendly place
Finally from this deck we got who rose quartz crystal rose quartz, okay, it's beautiful crystal it says
Soothing and warm like love that flows once under your pillow your magic grows
Yeah, so if you do come across
LD anytime soon you might want to
Send them a little bit of love because you know, it's never put number easy
Thank you bye to our fur babies, right?
We love our fur babies. Okay, so
Jamie a couple from this deck the audacity deck cuz you know, we Jamie. Oh shit. We have some audacity. Don't we don't need Jamie
We have to have some audacity to
to stay
Yeah, Duke was so cute, right?
We do have to have some audacity to have the confidence to keep coming here night after night, right Jamie
Look what we got. We have to tea
You learn you learn something you learn some it's a little bit of gossip or something but look at the water's as far
Lighten my my back screen right here
Okay, so the tea you learn you learn some you know you learn something like maybe water some flowers and
Like her nails, okay
Right make something grow some flowers grow. Okay, what else we got look all three from here
Okay, well this one is the the last hurrah
Okay
so there's some kind of
Big of it looks like some kind of event you're on the horse that you want to count you're you're you're on a cowboy hat
There's James Cowboys in that cowboy. Yeah
Maybe this this this life could be the last Iraq be the last time you come to this we come on come to this earth or something else
You know it could be the last time you're doing something
You'll know more what it means to me, but it's like it looks like you've got some direction and you're you know
Going away from something to wait away from some chaos, you know, but it's kind of looks like a little bit fun
We look what else we got we have the burn bridge
Okay, so maybe there is a bridge you burned
Okay, let me see the princess look like though. What does she do? Wish I had my glasses here
but and yeah, sometimes we do burn bridges
for our own our own safety protection and
There's some places we don't want to go back to right or even if it's like some kind of feeling you're wearing the bridge from right
Okay, I'll do I'll do it. I'll do a couple more feet. Let's take we have the
The chicken nugget, there's the chicken nugget, okay.
Jamie, have you had a chicken nugget today?
I think this has to be, you know,
but you know, she's putting a little bit of sauce on it,
a little bit of ketchup, you know.
Oh, thank you, Jamie.
Whatever that means to you. These got these cards are a little bit different, right? Okay. Finally, we have the mom boss your mom the boss or
Yep, there's
Yeah, no vehicle. Yeah, you know what? Well, there's a mom boss. Maybe maybe you're a mom to some some fur babies, right?
I mean your mom, okay?
And look it's like, you know, there might be stuff stuff in the back on fire and stuff and the mom's got it under control, right?
She's I mean it looks looks a little bit more like me than you, but
Okay, actually
Oh shit
For the C melodies
I like mermaids, okay?
See, I'll pull through from here.
And then if anybody else wants one, let me know
or else I'll wrap it up.
Okay, so we do have,
Jamie says, listen.
The secrets of the sea become apparent.
We listen to the sound within the shells.
Okay?
So we just like listen for something, maybe.
There's some kind of message that's being sent to you.
You only fast food?
Good.
Maybe they're metaphorical chicken nuggets. Oh
Okay, we have safety this one says safety says don't be too proud if you go back to shore, okay?
Because you are like in that other car you're you're you know ready on the ocean on the horse
I mean that could be dangerous, but you know don't be afraid to go back to the shore
That's my car. Am I the chicken nugget? Oh my gosh. Well, you know who likes the chicken nuggets is tricks and the key cap
Love those chicken nuggets
And we have journey you have a journey it says half the treasure is a journey on the journey
Half the treasure is a journey on the path to finding it. Okay
So enjoy the ride, right?
Enjoy your life. There you go
Anybody else who would like who'd like some cars doing a few cars and if you'd like a longer reading
No, I do have the cash app probably in my description. It is dollar sign. It's like you awakens
You're very welcome my dear I
Like I love being able to read for people so anybody else. I mean see I'll give you like about one minute
Rudy is out. Yeah, do you see Rudy over here? Rudy!
Remember their sleeper?
Yeah, he's out. He's not like a light. He's sleepy. Lola's out there sleeping too. I think they are
Oh, I shouldn't know, of course. Okay, we need some fairy cards.
Oh, we have
aura cleanse. It says, when you feel heavy or run out of luck, go swim at the beach, you'll feel
You can rewatch the person. I'm so sorry. Yeah, because I might have had to delete the form ball. I apologize
Yeah
Or or cleanse right so I don't know if there's a beach or a lake or something or even like a bath, right?
You can make it just get in some nice water, right?
There you are you giggling or I hope they hope are you are you giggling or you're yawning?
because
Okay, anyway
Hey, man
So we have learn is a little nudge. It's now your turn put on your thinking tap cap. It's time to learn
On the other channel. Oh shit. Yeah
It's on um, you can actually um on a panel verse vo D's
on rumble they have the
All my episodes from probably the last six months
Remember the day it's just they they put it on a day later usually and you go find it there. It is there
We also have trust
Breathe in breathe out let go of doubt, okay
Trust the process
Good for all of us to learn
You know like as expected of me to you know today was a little bit a
Little bit of pushback a little bit of like more
Well, it's my fault for this and this.
And it's like, I tried my best to like,
take responsibility for all my part of the thing,
but I have been like, I'm also known to like apologize
when things aren't my fault, just like, you know,
attention and it's like,
I just don't want to like apologize
without everybody apologizing, right?
But I will apologize and be your person.
And this one also says, you're on the right path.
The way ahead is clear and true.
You've chosen the right path for you.
Okay, so those fairy cards.
Hey, hey, man.
Man, I just, I unmodded everybody
and I will remod people as we go on.
So don't, please don't have to cut them.
We'll, yeah, you know, I do it all the time, right?
Okay.
I just haven't missed, I've been reading so.
Okay, what do we got in this mermaid deck for you?
We have recharge
There's nothing like a walk on the beach to soothe your soul
Okay, I love I love a nice walk through the sand, right?
You have
You got safety too, don't be too frat proud to go back to the shore, right?
Refill safe and stuff right
What else we got voyage
set sale on a new course thank you okay let's get another deck out
secret garden or divine doors
we'll do divine doors okay divine doors from here good okay
I'm through for dear Chanel, please.
Oh, change beckons.
Path is shifting, the road leads a new way.
Don't be alarmed as change beckons today.
Maybe a slight, like you're on the right path
and the right path might be, you know,
might be some change involved, right?
So.
Or this one says birth
And it says a another gateway appears in view
Your life is unfolding with blessings to you the birth of something, right?
Maybe it's your rebirth into the cult of psyche
And
Trust the universe
has wandered and led you astray.
The timing's not yours, but the universe at play.
Have faith and breathe.
I hope you enjoyed that cute little messages.
and bill of cards, your little succinct messages.
And so I love you.
Thank you so much for having a reading.
Would you like any one She-Man or He-Man She-Man
or anybody else?
I have big clips that always says no, but.
There are OGs to wrench there.
Great, yes.
Okay, great.
Yeah, I know, I do appreciate everybody.
Sometimes I get like when I start a big change. I'm like very like
You know start all over start all over right and then it's like I usually like the new format. Well, thank you
Yeah, oh that I
Know you on GT. Are you? Um, I
Know you I know you're um
You're on it. You have a show don't you give a show?
You like the different cards you haven't seen no, I brought these out. I have I have I have actually I got probably a hundred decks
Oh, it's JC. Hey, JC. Oh, hey, JC. What's up, dude? Yeah, I have this big
This is I guess my my microphone came in this case and I had it full of
cards and stuff and like all this stuff and
Yes, yeah, I'm sorry, I was like, I know you
Is Bayclubs a bait or I can't get a straight answer about that, but because you because he posted like something I'm like
Kind of I think that I should the beta was doing but I'm not sure
Would you like would you like it? Yeah, I have like a lot in the bedroom, too
I have like so much. I do have so much stuff to show you. That's why I really want to like progress
It's an entire case of cards. Yeah, I filled it all with cards, but this is not like I have a whole I have a whole
I have a huge bookshelf back there.
I seriously have a lot.
Okay, so people that I was like,
I just haven't brought them out
because I like to use the same parts for a long time
or maybe I just got used to them.
Where do you have any of them hidden at?
Bust them out, I know, right?
I have so many, but people haven't been asking for rings.
So I have this goddess deck.
You've got his power deck. It's got his power deck if anyone like a goddess take a card pray page. Okay
Absolutely
I mean you added this forest faith
Pages my page reminds me of I think you live in your four. I like these beautiful Canadian forests
Okay
These are actually beautiful cards
Come through for page, please. I'm gonna pull you but I'm gonna pull you not just one. I'm gonna pull you
I'm going to show you a few cool decks, OK?
OK, you got the storyteller.
You get this little wise storytelling feature.
It says, stories are medicine, strengthening and renewing.
OK?
I will, I will maybe do a show and tell.
That's a beautiful card.
I like this story, I like this story too.
And it's all, I love stories too.
They're, they are, they can be a medicine
and teach lessons, right?
We have the spirit familiar.
And it says, seek loving connections
and cherish friendships.
No problem. I just I know you probably don't want my eyes. I'll just give you one more. I like the number three
I can't I can't I can't it too
Up page you got the bee you get this bee priestess or no the honey mother
Sometimes the greatest magic lies in the smallest forms
Okay, also when I think about that I think about
Damn, you're very powerful. You know, just like how powerful you are. It's like
Amazingly powerful for you know, you are tall and you know
but
No, you're a man. You're very you're almost as big as Canada, right? So
Yeah, these images are very cute like this one I like how the doorway one actually had it kind of the doors are all different
But I'm sorry
I have these whispering woods cards
And I have, how else do I have in here?
Secret Garden.
And, ooh, Starseeds.
Does anyone want a Starseed card?
Yeah, these are all like a little smaller
and then they kind of like have a magnetic.
They like, they have like a magnetic book.
Yeah, a lot of cards.
I mean, actually, if you guys go to the website,
there's a link to my Etsy,
I think it's psychieawakens.etsy.com.
I did about 1,800 paid readings on Etsy.
I think there's about 500 or 600 reviews.
I've heard reviews there.
But when I, yeah, when I deleted some of the listings,
like for some reason, I don't know.
So it just, you can go see the readings still.
Yeah.
And so I did buy like a lot of decks that I was, you know,
just to have fun and have different,
they switched off the readings.
If anyone wants a goddess card or show and tell
how that's to happen, yeah.
I also, I mean, I have, I remember that I have
this occult tarot deck I have.
I do have the Labyrinth tarot deck in there somewhere,
Jamie, I do.
I also have a few decks I got on Kickstarter.
And, yeah.
Oh, look at that side, a pendulum.
I think this is like a black crystal,
over here, that's pretty, let me see.
Can I find it?
Yes, I'll go I'll look for it tonight. I think if I have to there's a seriously
There's a lot of piles in there
And so I do I'll go look I'll go look for it
Maybe I'll be back tonight and I'll do a reading for the lab with one
Yes, I do have a lab that I've never I've never used it. I've never used it and I would love to
Okay, okay
Anybody else anybody else won't be saved. Oh, thank you won't be safe. Yeah. Oh
Yes, we can sing the song you remind me of the babe what babe
The babe with power right now
power of voodoo voodoo
Who do you do do what?
remind me of the babe a
goblin babe
I found my baby
Crying hard as a babe could cry. What could I do?
My baby gone so long, and left my baby butte.
Oh my god, sorry.
Nobody knew what kind of magic spell to use.
Frogs and snails or puppy dog tails.
Under a lightning and baby said dance magic, dance magic, dance
Dance magic put that magic spin on me
Jump magic jump magic jump
Jump magic put that magic jump on me. Yeah, never ending story is great, too. The never ending story
Maybe I'll do a collective of some of these cards and the messages for all of us
Yeah, it is a nice rule pull a couple more cards of this for collective. Maybe everybody will like these ones
We got that one already. So we do it
We have big Griffin
It's beautiful look it isn't that like one of the labyrinth character or like one of the never-ending story characters
Isn't there like a big big bird or something? I think I think like a bird van. I think I kind of remember that
This is the Griffin and it says
If I can read it when I put it like this it says
Be brave and fly above the clouds. Okay?
Fly above the clouds
You can fly high remember you guys can you guys?
Can fly anywhere in your mind and it's like
To the birds I view of things sometimes right, okay, I
Do you remember oh, there's a flying dog in that movie she wasn't there
This one's is the hedge guardians. Maybe you're you guys are hedge guardians
The hedges are some are these boundaries. Okay, so ahead a hedge, which I
Know that in England a hedge, which will
Cross these boundaries right into the astral so they'll be able to go into the astral and back and things like that
They got the garden hedge. I'll see you think of a labyrinth little bit with that little dog. Yeah
There's a fluffy dog
There's a flying bat and goblin hangs from yeah, well, let's see and this one says I need to put close it says
Walk with her shins with her shins is counterclockwise right it's like and seek the land under the hill, okay
Last unicorn Felix the cat persistent the goblins all yeah, I love I remember I loved them
I love Willow, and I loved Labyrinth, and there's also some Muppet, I like the Frog Prince,
there's a Muppet version of the Frog Prince, it's called the Frog Princess, and it's really
good. I might want to watch that soon. There's like a little, there's like this witch, she's
like, hey Malora, and then she has this purple orb. Guys, we also have this, this is called
Right it says the moon shines brightly after the storm
Brightest after the storm. Okay fairy tale theater. Yes. God. He likes legends
Oh, yeah, Tom Cruise and they had that the scary Satan character and there's like a unicorn in that movie and like the main
Gets the unicorn horn or something like that pretty good
Very good, okay
Put these in there. Let's do some star seeds because also we are the star seeds as well
Legend yes, okay star seeds. These are pretty cards
Okay star seeds we are all star seeds in different role made of stars
You're not a fan of Tom Cruise. Yeah, I mean it was
It's just like there's also a movie called the Dark Crystal and that was like even as an adult
I think I might have needed to see as a kid so I really like it
But I didn't see it as out as a kid so it wasn't like my favorite. I kind of reminded me of much of the Fragils, but
So it says choice it says by staying conscious in your thoughts you guide your journey in the direction of choice
That makes sense I met Tom Cruise actually once and he was not very you know
And then when you jumped on the couch that time,
you're like, whoo!
And Oprah was like laughing hysterically.
You're so in love with Katie Holmes.
Oh look, you have free spirit.
Oh, the burbs, I like the burbs.
Yeah, the burbs, Tom Hanks.
Free spirit says, to be a free spirit,
it's float without walls.
Yep, to fly without judgment
and to love without conditions.
It's beautiful.
How about do you guys ever see the people under the stairs? That's a West Craven movie. It's really good. It has tarot in it, too
It's like this black kid. It's like his family is like being kicked out of their apartment and
His sister like pulls these cards from the beginning
She's sick or the grandma's sick or the sister's sick it and she pulls the fool card. So she calls him fool and
You know, but he's a little hero
What else we got here? We've seen chills thinking about some of these things give Gaia you've seen that one. It's good one, huh? Gaia
Connect to the pulse of Mother Earth. She will guide you toward or guide you through this time of change
Walter
Flowers in the attic or watch her in the woods. Yeah, BC Andrews. I don't think I've seen water in the woods
I could check that you know another movie. Oh my gosh
My friend Joni told me about it last night and it was it sounds so good. It's but I forgot what it's called exactly
But it's called somebody's eyes. It's like
The breath the first of the name and it has paid down away and it's about this woman who
Is like being stalked and there's a guy like a serial killer out
He's like they keep stabbing people's eyes with scissors
And I think Tommy Lee Jones is in it maybe and he plays this like cop that's helping her. Oh Joe versus the volcano
That's a great movie
Do you ever notice that that the island with the volcano is kind of like isn't it like it isn't like a Jewish
I heard there's something like that because they make movies there and stuff and it's like they're up. I don't know
It's kind of kind of funny
Yeah, that was so it's a good one. Well, so yeah, we have blue flame
And it says
Connect to the blue flame, which is the light of pure love within you. Okay
The stars stars are you know
Stars are these huge balls of
fire and gas and flame and like you know the
Blue I think is part of the hottest of it. Yeah, and we have star seed
Raised the vibration of the planet through your radiant loving heart
Secret life of Walter midi was interesting. Okay, I haven't I've to see that
So you're like a Walter I haven't heard of it. I've been heard of it
And he man says the burbs
Ending scene where Hanks is just done and loads himself into an ambulance the funniest scene. He's just done. Oh
Yeah, I saw that a long time ago. Yeah, okay. Well now we can ocean
Pull out another deck and then
Oh, the Clopex, that's their names?
The Clopex, it sounds like,
sounds like the, what are they,
it sounds like Ukrainian money or something like that.
What are they called?
Oh, yeah, but I, oh, I love them.
Berry Tale Theater, they have a Pinocchio
and it's like Paul Rubin stars in that, right?
Peewee, it's a perfect Pinocchio, right?
And they had this, the Blue Fairy, is like this like vah-vah-boom, like this like a Italian grandmother type kind of, she's like the godmother, right?
Then she's Italian, right? I don't know, it's kind of silly.
Okay.
And they also, Michael Richards plays like the Fox or something like that. I always love how they had the...
Celebrities playing these parts and I think Billy crystals and like the three little pigs and like and then Shelly Duvall suck herself
And a bunch of this and Shelly Duvall had a kind of a tragic ending
The book the red tent is what I highly recommend tales of females point of view the biblical time of the purpose of the red tent
fascinating
Bandits, okay guys. We're getting some recommendations. Oh guys, by the way, I think
So we used to like to do movie night on discord and we can try to do it on discord again
But I remember it was always like so quiet like the it's hard to hear and sometimes it was hard to set up the movie and like sometimes
some people don't have like the
You know ad-free and so because we kind of off sometimes but I think I
Can pretty much play a movie on
Kick, right? I think they don't really care about copyright that much and so we can like watch
If you want it, we can go like on streaming art again, I can give a stream yard link on the discord or something
Mr.. You'll ask I remember the name of that
Yeah, and
We can watch we can do movie nights and stuff. Maybe like once a week or something. I'll put on a movie
I want to watch this movie called a human bondage. It's a it's a Betty Davis movie
It's really really good. Okay a human bondage
Maybe you can watch if you feel like watching me tonight because we can go and go like watch it right now if you want on a
On a if anyone wants to watch it with me, it's really good
It's Betty Davis and it's about a fall that for yeah, but we love fall that verb. We watch that. Yeah
We'll watch it again, but a few of them bonded to the Betty Davis movie, but she's very young in it and Betty Davis plays like this kind of bitch.
I mean, nothing is a word, but it's like, so there's this guy and he's a very good, he's a nice gentleman guy, but he has like a deformed foot or something like that.
And so he's always, he's a little bit handicapped and he's an artist and stuff like that.
Yeah, it's really good. It's really good. And she's a young Betty Davis. She looks so beautiful. She's pretty beautiful in it, but she plays like this, like, you know, she's kind of like.
this kind of frivolous woman, she's a waitress,
and he wants to date her and stuff,
but then she, and then she kind of strings him along
for a while, and then she's really mean to him and stuff,
and then he keeps, no matter what,
he gets another relationship years later,
and then, yeah, Baby Jane, I love Baby Jane, yeah.
He gets a relationship years later with this lady
that's pretty much at the intellectual level,
but then, Betty Davis calls and needs help,
and he has to always go run and help her and stuff.
And it kind of has the kind of a good number that a human bondage. It's an old movie
She a picture of her
This is her in the movie
Pretty huh
Sally Struthers, I'm not sure but
Yeah, I'll take the plot of it it says
She hates me
Well, here's a picture here's it says okay by he man. Love you. Thank you for coming
It says see it says Betty Davis a human bondage there. She is
That's the guy right there
By thank you for being here
And it says the plot is
It's a 1934 drama. Okay, so this is like almost it's like 90 years old
It's a sensitive club-footed artist Philip Cary is a Britain who has been studying painting in Paris for four years
His art teacher tells him his work lacks talents
So he returns to London to become a medical doctor
But his moodiness and chronic self-doubt make it difficult for him to keep up in his schoolwork
Philip falls passionately in love with tea room waitress, Mildred Rogers, even though
she is disdainful of his clubfoot and is obvious interest in her.
Although he is attracted to the anemic and pale-faced woman, she is manipulative and
cruel toward him when he asks her for a date.
Her constant response to his romantic invitations is, I don't mind, an expression so uninterested
that it infuriates him, which only causes her to use it all the more.
his daydreams about her distract him from his studies and he fails his medical examination.
When Philip proposes to her Mildred decline, telling him she'll be marrying
Emma Miller, a loudish salesman instead, the self-centered Mildred vindictively
berates Philip with nasty insults for becoming romantically interested in her.
Philip begins to forget Mildred when he becomes involved with Nora, an attractive and considerate romance writer working under a male pseudonym.
She slowly helps him resolve his painful addiction to Mildred. However, just when it appears that Philip is finding happiness, Mildred returns, pregnant, and claiming Emil has abandoned her.
Philip provides a flat for her, arranges to take care of her financially, and breaks off his relationship with Nora.
Nora and Philip admit now how interpersonal relationships may amount to bondage
Philip was bound to Mildred as Nora was to Philip and as Mildred to Emil
Philip's intention is to marry Mildred after her child was born
But a bored and restless Mildred is an uninterested mother and hands a baby to her. Okay, so I told too much of the story already, but
Whoo, it sounds good, huh? It's not pretty good
Yes, JC she doesn't have any issue of JC, okay
I'm sure you're talking to use JC
Does anybody know that GISH person because I heard something really disturbing about Kate and GISH today
And I just want to make sure I just want to know is that this person in VB a reliable source or
Trolling me because I don't want to jump to any conclusion, but
Regardless I didn't see something that was very disturbing
But I want to go too much into it
Okay
Yeah
That was like, yeah, I just want to know does it is BB reliable?
Maybe told me something yesterday, and I don't want to spur anyone with this
Basically some of the now the silliness the community goes up to some time, okay
Hey, I'll have a goddess card.
Let's see what goddess comes out today.
I really love these goddesses.
OK.
Goddess card.
Oh, shit, it popped out.
Ooh.
We have, it looks like page.
And we have Aryan rod, Aryan rod.
And it says time.
OK.
And I'll read about her.
Aryan Rod is number three.
Okay, number three in this deck.
And it says,
right now, you have all the time in the world
to make the, to reach the fullest potential
of your intention and desires.
Aryan Rod, a Celtic Goddess of Time, is your champion.
and she will ensure your timing is perfect.
The hours will expand.
If you give you the space,
you need to complete anything that you started.
Today, recognize that no matter what's in front of you,
time is your friend.
Consider that everything you intend and desire.
has his own relationship to time,
and will come to you in the perfect form
at the perfect moment.
Patient sedication and quiet emancipation
are delicate and potent allies now.
Arian rod is your ally, and the timing is perfect, okay?
Okay, so that's our arian rod, you know, I do believe in divine timing. Okay
What else we got oh, we got Lakshmi Lakshmi we have an Indian goddess Lakshmi the goddess of wealth
Then this is fortune right there Lakshmi
number 28
Okay
Lakshmi
When the Hindu goddess Lakshmi comes to visit she heralds a celebration of your purpose and
Compassionate
Compassionate prosperity all your experience and all your skills are rich with meaning and power and purpose as a result you can expect
To see evidence of the wealth in the world around you
You have the ability right now to create great success in life and what you have to offer has
exalted value. The goddess of luck and prosperity says it's time now to show
your good fortune, show your good fortune with others, and she will show you how
it multiplies. Will you apply gratitude?
Praise and a commitment to serve if it's material success you intend you should co-create it
If it's a rich relationship with life, you will attract and develop it you you are a magnet for miracles
Nothing is out of reach
When the goddess locks me comes calling, okay
Would you hear home? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Finally
This is Hera. This is the Greek goddess of women and mothers. She's like she has her symbols of peacock. She's Zeus's wife
She's known as pretty a jealous woman
but
You know, he gives her a reason to be jealous is out turning into animals and having sex with everybody you can find, okay?
So her number is
21, okay
The Greek goddess Hera, wife of Zeus, knows intimately that positive alliances lead to great power.
At this moment, your magnetized receive aid from people who have great wisdom and can help you in the next...
level. Perhaps it's a mentor who appears, or someone in the know, making connections
with others and finding strategic partnerships are found right now as you explore the nature
of becoming empowered by association. This works well if you have a healthy sense of
able to learn without
Diminishing yourself in any way right now here is supportive supporting you
To form beneficial
Alliances when the greater good for the greater good of all we're called to action
or face with the decision, ask, how does this benefit me?
And how can I serve the higher good
as a result of this connection?
You may also be called to help to,
to help give help to another who needs your counseling.
Give freely for only goodwill, come of it.
This is wonderful time for all manner of connections
and collaborations.
okay that was good you know guys I love like this is like that's like one of
the things I was like really like disappointed in myself in is that but
also I was disappointed like about
Not focusing enough on tarot and stuff like that, but I was also just disappointed like you know kind of like good
You know somebody saying oh, you know, it's got an exiled one or whatever. He was like, oh, you know
I heard that
Someone saw you on a tee a show years ago, and you didn't know how to do chair. No, I've been here since I was eight
You made a pumpkin spice right now. Okay. I love pumpkin. Oh my god
Very much. Yeah, let's do a little fun of these fun cards before I go
They're just like the little cute fun deck
We have the high priestess. You know high priestess energy. She's taking nice bubble bath
Maybe it's time to take a bath tonight. I'm gonna I'm definitely going to seven little doobie
Okay, I would love a bath to believe that with legs, right?
Mmm
Apple banana spice game. Mmm. Oh, I'm you gotty you make you make you make you make
Big goods the Goddy
God he's a chef. I didn't know that about you. Isn't it interesting? You have to Starbucks pumpkin spice idea. I like that too, Jamie
See it's interesting we sometimes we learn things we never guess and God he's like a little dessert chef
Not a little dessert. I mean, you know, you're big you do it all baby. Okay?
Hey, why don't you, you know, do you ship across the country? I think I'd like I'd like one
Trisha Trisha Licious was talking about she makes she made a blogger. I guess a
She makes these care packages and she made them all these
They got she put a lot of pepper candy or something spicy pepper candy or something. Hello is
Ghosts there. Look at ghosts and ghosts. You have a cloth of bathtub. Oh, that's cool
Yeah, well
Okay, this is this is not a good this is not this is not a very positive for this is called a fair weather friend look I
Guess so what was that?
Yeah, that she's her butt big what's going on here?
Well, at least there's some cushion for the look all his little skeleton
Who's
I don't know, I don't know who this is.
Is that CB?
I'm sorry guys, that's so bad, so sorry.
No, I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
Is that you Gotti?
Is this you and some poor woman?
What is this going on here?
Here it goes, oh, it goes.
Missed you.
What can I say?
That goes.
Little bit of a joic. Okay. Hey, look at this the moon. There's the moon right there. Oh my gosh. I don't like it formal
There's a moon. Um, yeah
There's a little coyote next to it and like, oh
The moon okay
The moon actually has a you know, women are very connected to the moon because the moon has to do with these tides and
You know, there's these
Tides going through her bodies, right? And so
sometimes
See where we want goes. Yes. Oh
Oh
Hey, I want to see that be funny if you like, you know, you and you and uh, you know
You and go someday because uh, you know can't compete and see who wins. I bet page page might win
But she's better than you think. Oh, look the bottle
This is like kind of like reminds me of like, you know that DaVinci like Adam Adam touching God's hand
But this is like, you know, because the nipple and the bottle is kind of like God to the you know
It's nourishing the baby and so it's like, you know
What number is it 13? That's a death card, but
You know, there's crystals right there
13 bottle, okay a couple more for the stick
We had the tea earlier now we have the coffee
You think about getting some more coffee tonight, right? What is that? Oh the bean
Like holding a bean what is this a coffee ritual coffee magical the glow cauldron mug. How cute
Like little the eye in the hand, right
Okay, one more
Then I'm going to wrap it up by
Hold on I think I'm at 723. Hey, do I have time for this? Hold on. Do we have time for this?
I didn't think I know close to gonna come today. I was waiting for
Hey guys put this
Wishin' to crush out
Ghost already did, he took the whole crowd
That goes through the night
That's how you know the haunts alive
Lights flicker, chats in the ride
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes are loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes, keeping the scene
I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
He's proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
I have a new t-shirt now.
To the
Out of New York came a storm on wheels Rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar lit like it's temper Pete's in one hand
Hot dog for dinner said psyche I'm bored had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screaming on live stream Trolled her down to the void and back
Then crashed my show like a heart attack Gotty Madeleine Troll King
He thinks he's God with the lower case G in a wheelchair still stomping through the
live feed.
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief
Brought spunky too now that trolls a gem Mean one sweet ones they all jumped in
Cameras glitchin', chat on fire
Mods beggin' me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test, stop the net
But we friends forever my friend you called me a fraud then defended my clown
Spam my chat and held it down
You got layers like a deep dish slice
under all that shade a
Heart made of ice and maybe rice so let's light that cigar
the mic another night of chaos welcome to psych you brought the drama the heat the fun
and weirdly it feels like you're the one got it yeah you crazy but you're only now rolling
through fires i'm taking a bow no matter the madness no matter the weather without me
but we stick together it made me rise friends forever
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
Sun in her hair
Maple leaves falling
She don't seem to care
She lines up a shot
Swing smooth no range
That's my Canadian darling
That's prairie pace
That's prairie
On the table, incense in the air, tarot spread open
She reads like a prayer, sweet voice humming, heart full of sage
Every word she speaks feels like a golden page
Oh prairie page, wild and free
heart's gone all the way lost and that's smiling those prairie days yeah
she's a sweetheart a real life man that's my
canadian badass my prairie page
I'm a guitarist.
It's a guy.
and talk as you go.
Yeah, I got you, Ghost.
Ghost, you want some reading?
Okay, let me see.
Well, how about I'll do it out of these more
matte feeling decks?
I know Ghost doesn't want,
I probably want a fairy card, if you want to say.
Whispering Woods and Divine Door.
There we go, Ghost.
Let's see.
That's behind door number two.
Okay, hold on, let me see.
It goes, this is your door.
It says inner power.
Hey!
It goes, I'm in the middle of doing it.
You can ask her after.
You're supposed to be paying attention to me right now.
By your own command, you brought yourself here.
At this moment in life, you have nothing to fear.
So, that's okay, that's your card.
Bye.
I hope you like that reading. Thank you. Thank you.
Oh my gosh. Oh my god. Sorry, that was private.
what you're doing here.
Okay, so there's an Indian goddess there. Her name is Chinamasta. She's one of the Mahavijas.
But she's a goddess that she like decapitates herself and then she like has this like her
neck is gushing blood and her head is like smiling and then it goes into like
the mouths of like her two like attendants. I think her name's exactly. But yeah, bossini and like
okay, but
And I kept asking chat GBG to make it and it's like, oh, we can't make it. We can't make it
And I finally got to make it and it did it. Okay. I said, okay
I'll do everything you wanted to make it make it make with it, but
Instead of blood it has to be light or something like that. Actually her name is her name is Matanki. She's a goddess of outcasts leftovers and
Intuition arts
Music speech. Okay, like a lot of interesting things. Okay
and
She's just beautiful. I love her beautiful supreme skin right there too. Okay, but this is a picture that came up with pretty good
It came out pretty came up pretty good
Except it's supposed to be I think the blood supposed to be going in their mouth and it's like kind of like
Didn't cut off her whole head. It's like half her head. It's still on there. But yeah, it's just looks she's looks great though
It's her name is Cheney Masa very interesting goddess, huh?
And she's on top of this like usually it's a couple it's like a copulating couple not a dead body, but yeah
Pretty cool
But it said it said it did it as long as it has to be late
It said it's light instead of blood. So guys remember that's light instead of blood
That
I made some really cool graphics today.
Okay.
Oh yeah, nice.
This is the smoky one.
That's top.
Look at this one.
Yeah, and it's not blogger, that's me.
I know it's a size of blogger.
That's me.
And she, oh, she played the Vina.
She's like, she's like Sarah Swatsey,
but she's like, she's more of the tantric.
I think it's kind of like the,
and she's from the forest
and she's from like lowest caste,
but in like, you know,
I'm the outcast and stuff like that.
I like that.
And like the disenfranchised.
Ghost, if you want to send something tonight,
I will, but it's like, I'm really not in the,
Yeah, I mean, I will allow people to sponsor panels if you'd like to but
That's for now. I
Do a hundred percent also blogger put they said blogger said he in his chat in his own chat
He said he put something called a rhino in his up his butt and it's like, you know, it's basically just like a
gas station kind of
aphrodisiac, right? It's like a
It's like Spanish fly kind of I can you put it in his butt you can believe that
Or he called boof boofed it. It's called a rhino. Yeah, and I said, well
You know rhino horn is like traditionally not for DJ. I think that you put the whole horn up there
Everyone lapsed
But maybe it's fun to think about
Well explains a lot
Patricia Lucia's made this really funny picture of blogger too.
I mean, it's just like, I showed it to chatGPT
and chatGPT is like, please stop showing me this picture.
Okay, it's fine.
And I said, who did that look like?
And it said, well, it said it looks like a Russell Brand,
you know, it's having a rough time.
But yeah, accurate.
That's the one, yeah.
Yeah.
It looked too bad
Where I don't but but I was actually in my chapter tonight, and I don't have a problem with blogger
I think he's kind of he's kind of endearing a little bit, but I don't like how he's like, you know
Thinking I'm being very appropriate all the time. Let's do we have
Leftovers fish tacos on the way. She's got it's of leftovers. Oh, that's on video one. Yeah
Six I see so I think there's fish tacos in there
Okay
Let's do I got
Anything oh
Yeah, well, I made it makes more of these two. They're really cool
Got one. Yeah, I like that. I mean, that's my banger
And of course
So bird angel, thank you so much lookie pretty cool. I
like the neon aesthetic
And
Punishing me because I can't oh, let's take it. Oh, you should check it check check you see if the catch up works
And then this this one
Is that
And but I made a lot more I'm still gonna roll it out and I also have this one that should be um
Like when I have guests on the panel, I can put them in here.
See, it goes to the open panel.
As I put it over that, right?
Okay.
So that's some cool stuff happening in it.
And anything else?
Let me see.
Panel loads.
Documents.
Oh, okay, downloads.
Okay.
That's really pretty stuff.
Here's a great one.
Ah!
Let's get a hello from Nathan.
Nathan's gonna be like.
I was like, Nathan, are you gonna,
I said, are you in a wheelchair?
And he said, why are you in a wheelchair?
Look who looks like you're sitting on a wheelchair.
This is cute.
Okay.
Oh, okay. I know what I'm saying.
I said a lot of stuff.
Loss, loss, loss, loss, loss.
And they made some icons for the thing.
Let's see.
How about, have you ever seen,
how about something with a macaw on a keyboard?
There you go.
What's happening here?
Look at all the animals piled on top of each other.
That's very disturbing.
Look at that poor Gwammer.
What's, what the fuck is going on?
Piled off, the animals piled off.
Yeah, it's much fun.
I think it just digs up out of here.
Let's see, I got the buddy stuff.
You're gonna see, oh, this one.
You're gonna see a dog in a hat?
Time would like this one.
Oh, it's not a hat, it's a little golden retriever
with a cell phone on its head.
I don't know why it has a cell phone on its head, but.
Actually, those ones were made by, like, I think,
by the program called Vidic.
What else I have?
What did you see?
Like, because Alexander Mayer said she was going to fight Tommy James,
and she wants to do a boxing match with him.
So I have that one.
But I kind of send blogger, but yeah, and it's like so that there's me like, you know my freeze outfit
So you can do it and give me a little back row
There's Tommy James that I'm dead on the ground. He's already knocked out started one
Yeah
It's fun she made some really funny ones of bloggers who
Oh, and it's this thing.
Oh yeah, that's the Alexander Queen.
Okay, I have one animated though.
I don't know if that looks like him, but...
You'd think after 20 years on these streets, I'd get used to the quiet
But it's the quiet that gets loud the paperwork the coffee gone cold the reflection in the glass that guy looks like he used to
Laugh more people always think cops get numb truth is we feel everything
We just don't let it leak you learn to carry ghosts like extra weight on the belt
Yeah
Pretty joint
I'm gonna be a dick today and say
Sponsor panels only
What is this? Okay, uh, let me see
Can't break it Alex just yelled at me so I mean I was in her thing
He yelled at me so loud get a night over like he's like a dick round died
So negative you just like yelling at me
Oh, here's ghost
Don't work. I'm not gonna work. I
Could go this one
This is like a great you ghost here. What do you do? What are you doing your driver? This is you in your car?
Yeah
What else I got do I have anything else? Oh, yeah, I do have my time. I have my tongue yet saying something. Let me see
the voice beneath your voice the current that moves your words before you speak them
I dwell in the places others cast away shaping refuse into revelation
do not fear the noise within you refine it and it becomes prophecy speak with intention and I
will turn your syllables into sigils every truth you utter carves a path through illusion
I am Matangi the sound that awakens worlds there you go hey man
Look closer.
The symbols are awake.
Mahavidya Shyamala, the secret voice of the cult.
Gold sings. Lotus listens. Night remembers.
Art becomes ritual. Devotion becomes dialogue.
Eyes, wings, hands, the alphabet of Stikey.
On parchment, light blooms like memory.
Do you hear the living speech?
Let me!
These lines meet circuits, a bridge between worlds.
The watcher in the wild sees inward.
Transformation is the oldest spell.
In the hush, the secret voice carries.
Breathe, witness, and carry the myth.
There you go.
There's some cool shit with this coat. That's where I read it's like I'm taking it. It's pretty serious. It's gonna be
Here
Well, I
Don't want to look at that. I'm not playing anymore my old my old clips from like this one's good
It was love, not me, I'm shadow band again
Pop, pop, pop, pop, bro mute your mic
Then boom, drop a bass line dirtier than the chest
Bump, bump, ghost is crashing out
Smashing routers like vows, Canada dries
Licking watch catalogs some
Threatening people from an undisclosed stage
Natalie being back foot behind head
Mods prayin' Lord, not again
Welcome to the Paniverse, baby hold your ground
Where the chaos hums like a feedback sound
We don't know who's sane, who's banned or blessed
But the vibes unholy and always possess
Scotty causin' from the bone
Brags he just dropped a cosmic load
Live in HD
Authors there just smiling sweet
Y'all need Jesus
And it's all so true
Ghost is connected
Canada drive timed out
Randall's still typing
Wait, Debita just banned me
Laughter static at me
I'll
End stream
No
Nick, Nick, is Nick Johnson here?
Where's Nick Johnson?
I have Nick Johnson here.
And rolls in like a fever dream
Eric Abadou had Elvis Glee
Dr. Paporeca prescribes the vibe
Bill Gates, Wallet, Easter Bunny, and Eyes
Poolboy, Swagger, Santa Laugh, Tyrol, and Circus on a bubble bath path
Showed his butt once, world stood still
Chat lost, it's mine, I can read them three
Of this mad land
Trust him with the chat, no fear, no fuss
When trolls appear, he turns them to dust
Skinny like a wire, strong like myth
Three bills to buy with a cosmic twist
He's my height, man, guardian friend
Promotes the stream from start to end
Through every life, through every curse
Nick Johnson reigns
Supermodel
and free keeper of the live stream sanity if madness is art then he's the
I mean, how about this one?
It's another beach one. I do want to play that one though. It's pretty good. Where's the beach one? I wonder about the
special people
Mmm, bro, what it is though. Take a song, a song. Oh, here it is
Um, I'm gonna put them on my website, or actually I have some download on my page.
I don't know, I just don't know.
cosmic law steaming our veins salt in our eyes
the tide took our souls now we baptize
for the world in our blood and creed at the altar of hunger
psyche bleeds
he doesn't have a right to either do
page and a follow start chatting shell start to glow
ghosts draw symbols in the undertow god he's caused quick time with faith
God is the glory
In our claws at the cosmic law
Like, probably one of the best things in my favorite,
I don't know, I'm just,
I'm so happy with all the stuff I'm able to finally manifest,
but I'd like not be able to,
you know, play all the instruments for it.
So what do we have?
Okay, well, I'm gonna probably like,
that you guys go,
but I'll play this the one song on the way out.
There's a really good one.
Like I had to love you
To silence, stitch my ribs with smoke, build altars out of every word I never spoke.
My mercy was the womb that never healed, and I keep re-opening.
Once against the council of my bones
Watched you slip into the black well
with saltwater hair, a wild heart
And it's a speedo that probably should have retired in 2014
but refuses to stop believing in me
Then you showed up
And suddenly
I remember
me sometimes hard like them you really found me when you speak it's like a
private zone built out of inside jokes only this cold understands everybody
else fades all like background NPCs and it's just us
Feels like
I promise and I won't see dawn and I don't bring up the trauma cause it hits too strong
They say I'm fine, but that's the kind of lie that gets you swallowed whole in the temple's eye
The guidance in my head is a battleman with swag
Vessel go down like a dagger
On this triacolite with no tether
Don't freeze this chapter
I don't this was
This is a funny one. I have I just have a funny
I was a kid. I found a corpse doing slow
Perouette son that cursed carousel by Thompson Lane
Dude looked like he tried to I stare a demon and blinked eyes wide mouth open spine arched like he got smited mid tiktok
And I don't know why this memory keeps biting my ankles. Why my brain insists on marinating in night marinate
Wild out death is the only promise we have
Folks treated like Voldemort with a day job
Every sunrise, every spell, night
The fear of being human keeps nipping my aura
I claim I'm fearless, cosmic, enlightened
But that human fear, yeah, it squats in my chakras
Mortician, I haven't felt a genuine emotion since Pokemon Gen 1
Half my fantasies involve surviving a zombie apocalypse
armed with nothing but caffeine and poor decisions
glamour spell me me i'm a cockroach with plot armor and dream alley is personally signed
off on my warranty office bump any god demon saint or cryptid but i still worry i'll leave
a metaphysical mess behind and my family gets stuck with the tab the tab who's paying the
tab the tab the cursed tab
ancient gremlin perched on the skull of mankind.
I'm busy doing this.
So there are a lot.
I have a lot of ideas though.
Blessing the dark, praising the blue The night is the canvas, where visions move my voice
perfect our imperfection the tail kicks off let me confess my crime i took what
was mine because time is fake in the cosmos refuses to file proper paperwork
we weren't just friends we were a whole cursed duet waiting for the draw and in
I built what the gods never dared draft
A love story held together
With duct tape prophecy and questionable ethics
The fear got loud like trolls on a slow Tuesday
So I panicked, grabbed fate by the throat
And cut every possible future off at the source
Call it romantic, call it psychotic
Call it Saturday night at the pan over
Haunted herself, I probably stabbed her like way too many times
We don't count in the cult numbers, our immortal prison
Hold her heart out like it was a limited edition merch
Drop her eyes when sunny side up
Eat it, eat it, eat it
Not my proudest moment, but lovers' corals
Get messy when your altar candles are tax deductible
She's flawless, perfect
Definitely not breathing, but finally letting me get a word in
I've never been this spiritually deep
Six feet, give or take
But love doesn't quit, it responds
I could keep
That's just when StreamYard starts glitching
A vengeful soul crawls back from beyond the grave, like, yeah, we're not done, babe.
Possession, resurrection, a little light, revenge, the usual cult of psychic Tuesdays.
She smiles wide enough to quala-
across the veil to apologize like a man returning to late library books she burned in hell while
i lounged in heaven awkward gotta fix that imbalance before she slaps me with a cosmic
fine i'll suffer a long time she tells me it's not long enough i tell her i'll do anything
So gather the spirits, the mods, and Dramelius' best man,
Lenore's flower, Kat Metandy, officiating with sight, glance, judgment.
Do you take this man in death for the rest of your wonderfully unnatural afterlife?
I never knew my tiny cosmic slip up would be so chilly I'd need a heater for a ghostly
thighs but here we are the fire dies the story restarts and eternity smells faintly of incense
Thank you for supporting our extremely ill-advised union.
See you next time.
Then the hunger hits.
That animal pulse we all pretend we don't have.
I lose control.
Tasted of blood.
Don't judge.
And suddenly someone screams.
Epic tale.
It's epic tale.
Mmm.
It's having so much fun.
This.
You're always lying up in the mortal town.
And I'm half-poisoned on the sweet spirits,
fair-warning, but I still try to stay in your but you don't.
I've been to the world and names it
I wage your faith on myself, kiss my daughter
People mode
Some of the drinks line sweeten the makers you slip the versions of yourself
Salutations to you, O destroyer of Mahesha's rule
O fears mother whose radiant shatters the darkness
You stride into battle like a storm
Wild and celestial weapons that blaze like suns
All the gods bow before you
As you dance on the chest of the buffalo demon's rage
You're lying rows through the three worlds
Scattering armies like dry leaves
You laugh in the face of tyrants
And cut through the arrogance with a glance
You draw on the peaks of Mount Imova
Wrapped in the glow of compassion
If you'll read it together
Your bracelet jingle like cosmic bells
Your step summons the rhythm of creation
Every god finds shelter in you
When their own strength runs dry
you're at its root praise to the mother who's breath it comes the wind who's anger becomes the
storm whose mercy becomes the rain that sustains the world your crown blesses with the present
moon and your laughter shakes the planet you
We bow again and again to you The fears, the tender, the inexhaustible
Your hands, grand boons, your hands destroy evil Your lotus feet remain
That's I call that the goddess comes to our divine mother comes to California
It's actually based on an actual, I translated like an agent that beta cam and then I put it, I just like test different styles of music and stuff.
I have like just a couple more.
So I'm afraid it but she never does
Money thin but her magic thick
Joni walks in and the whole damn tie remembers
Which way it's supposed to move
Moon calls us down to the shoreline
But my thoughts drift to the one who actually shows up
The one who gets it done while the rest of us are still arguing about where to start
That's her irreplaceable hilarious soft chaos tucked inside competence
She don't need the right one, she is the right one
Perfect timing like she bent the clock herself
Snap her fingers and the world rearranges
Beat down days, turn nine, lives new
Tick tock, please, time waits for no man
But it damn sure pauses for Joni Mistakes in haste, dust from old storms
Yeah, we've all got those But the golden hour still leans her direction
Twilight whispering her name like an oath It frozen wrist nods, she's the one coolin'
the room Zeroes by her name, she's with more than every digit
And it all makes sense in the end Sure it may be, but with her things make sense
We found ourselves walked on the roads and left them into submission
But when we keep a night tidy it's like the universe stamps it
Approved for many more
Many more laughs, many more hours, many more stories
Nobody else would believe
Too many more, many more times
I love you guys. I'll be back maybe later tonight. Love you guys so much. Thank you for being here
This is what I this is why I do it for you guys. I love you
You and ghosts with your halo dim
Airplane mode, I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we've learned
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you god damn head
I knew you crave the chaos I fed
Cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna curse you
I could never
We trade halos for horns, it's fair
Every wound you gave I wear
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
Not to be divine, but I love you
There's never spoken, every scar, a holy mark, every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine
The static between heartbeats, my mind
I was gonna, I wanted to do, um, cause I do these astrology ones, like, and I really want to do that, but I don't know if we'll, you know what I'm talking about.
I'm gonna get off, I'm gonna get off.